（POP音樂播放）
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
講師:(講演講者）護士應該監督
INSTRUCTOR: (ON SPEAKERS)\nA nurse should monitor
抗血小板藥物的哪些副作用？
for which side effect\nof antiplatelet medication?
A，血壓下降B，潮熱
A, drop in blood pressure.\nB, hot flashes.
C，血便D，視力模糊
C, bloody stools.\nD, blurred vision.
血壓
Blood pressure.
C，血便
C, bloody stools.
- （SIGHS） - （點擊）
- (SIGHS)\n- (CLICKS)
抗血小板，血便
Antiplatelet, bloody stools.
?抗血小板，血便\n? Antiplatelet,
bloody stools
?血便，血便\n? Bloody stools,
?Antiplatelet，血腥凳子哦，doo-dah日\n? Antiplatelet, bloody stools
Oh, the doo-dah day
?哦，doo-dah dayOh，doo-dah日\n? Oh, the doo-dah day
?抗血小板，血便?\n? Antiplatelet,\nbloody stools ?
（婦女在電視上講西班牙語）
(WOMEN SPEAKING SPANISH ON TV)
（SIGHS）觀看一些運動般的真人
(SIGHS) Watch some sports\nlike real men.
這是你足球情緒的10倍
This has 10 times the emotion\nof your football.
（在西班牙語中出現）
(SHOUTING IN SPANISH)
這太荒謬了
It's ridiculous.
嘿抱歉，有人沖我濕錢
Hey. Sorry, some surfer\ngave me wet money.
好吧，這是你的送貨
Well, here\nare your deliveries.
哦，我會最後拯救650賽普拉斯
Oh, and I would save\n650 Cypress for last.
（SIGHS）加拿大培根和鳳梨？沒有Ew
(SIGHS) Canadian bacon\nand pineapple? No. Ew.
嘿，他很可愛，你可能會很開心
Hey, he's cute,\nand you might have fun.
我沒有時間玩樂
I don't have time for fun.
那麼，你做錯了
Well, then\nyou're doing it wrong.
將其添加到列表中
Add it to the list.
COOK：這並不荒謬
COOK: It's not ridiculous.
這些故事來自現實生活
These stories come\nfrom real life.
瘋狂的事情一直都在發生
Crazy things happen\nall the time.
來吧，支持我
Come on,\nback me up on this.
我不看這個狗屎
I don't watch\nthis shit.
我甚至都聽不到它就像在我的abuela上工作一樣
I don't even hear it. It's\nlike working at my abuela's.
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
呵呵
Huh.
（笑著）
(CHUCKLING)
講師：當從患者的肺部抽吸粘液時，
INSTRUCTOR: When suctioning\nmucus from a patient's lung,
哪個動作完成了程式
which action completes\nthe procedure...
（HONKS）
(HONKS)
凱特：嘿，女孩們，來吧，我們走吧！
KATE: Hey, girls,\ncome on, let's go!
- 嘿，媽媽！ - 嗨，媽媽！
- Hey, Mom!\n- Hi, Mom!
移動！我們得走了！
Move! We gotta go!
真的，媽媽？標誌？
Really, Mom? The sign?
在車上尷尬，好嗎？
Be embarrassed\nin the car, okay?
我有八分鐘的時間讓這些比薩餅穿過小鎮
I've got eight minutes to get\nthese pizzas across town.
移動！
Move!
學校怎麼樣？
How was school?
- 艾米莉：很好 - 哦，不要小費
- EMILY: Fine.\n- Oh, don't tip 'em.
（婦女選擇）
(WOMEN CHEERING)
科林：改變計畫，先生
COLIN: Change of plans, sir.
我們只是遇到一些輕微的機械問題
We're just having\nsome minor mechanical issues.
我們將停靠在最近的地方進行一些維修
We'll dock at the nearest\nharbor for some repairs
我會安排
and I'll arrange to have
地毯專業清潔
the carpets\nprofessionally cleaned.
科林，不需要知道香腸是怎麼製作的！
Don't need to know how\nthe sausage is made, Colin!
-  COLIN：絕對正確，先生 - （手機鈴聲）
- COLIN: Absolutely right, sir.\n- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
（PAPI講西班牙語）
(PAPI SPEAKING SPANISH)
-  Papa Papa- Mmm-hmm\n- Papa. Papa.\n- Mmm-hmm.
講師：當擦拭糞便時，
INSTRUCTOR:\nWhen swabbing fecal matter,
護士應採取以下哪些預防措施？
a nurse should take which\nof the following precautions?
-  OLIVIA：再見，媽媽！ -  MOLLY：看到你，媽媽！
- OLIVIA: Bye, Mom!\n- MOLLY: See ya, Mom!
凱特：好吧，你的奶奶，好嗎？
KATE: All right, listen\nto your grandma, okay?
阿婆好！
Hi, Grandma!
而且，嘿，我要你去洗澡，奧利維亞！
And, hey, I want you\nto take a bath, Olivia!
- 用肥皂 - 奧利維亞：好的
- Use soap.\n- OLIVIA: Okay.
你不是這樣的人
You're not gonna\nbelieve this.
還記得我是怎麼從Les Mis唱的那首歌
Remember how I sang\nthat song from Les Mis
在聖詹姆斯才藝秀
at the Saint James talent show
大家都說我很棒？
and everyone said\nI was amazing?
好的，媽媽，你能不能在電子郵件中打字，
Okay, Mom, can you just\ntype this up in an e-mail,
因為我的另一份工作要遲到了
because I'm gonna be late\nfor my other job.
原來，一個製片人
Turns out, a producer
來自Eugene的高級Theatertouring公司就在那裡
from the Eugene Senior Theater\ntouring company was there.
他哭了
He had tears.
無論如何，他們的一個領導在淋浴，
Anyway, one of their leads\nfell in the shower,
他們希望我介入
and they want me to step in.
什麼？什麼時候發生這種情況？
What? When is this all\nsupposed to be happening?
我今晚要離開他們已經在科技領域
I'm leaving tonight.\nThey're already in tech.
不，媽媽，我的護理檢查不到一個月
No! Mom, my nursing exam\nis in less than a month
你同意幫忙
and you agreed to help.
我現在72歲如果我現在不跟隨我的夢想，我什麼時候會？
I'm 72. If I don't follow\nmy dreams now, when will I?
（SCOFFS）從不，媽媽！
(SCOFFS) Never, Mom!
我們搬到這裡的全部原因是我可以學習更多
The whole reason we moved here\nis so I could study more.
我已經考試過一次了
I already failed\nthe exam once.
不，不要內疚我
No, don't guilt me.
你不是唯一一個死去的丈夫
You're not the only one\nwith a dead husband.
爸爸沒死，你離婚了！
Dad's not dead,\nyou're divorced!
- 哦，我需要你照顧Fiona-（SIGHS）
- Oh, and I'm gonna need you to take care of Fiona.\n- (SIGHS)
狗窩不會帶她吃她的箱子有焦慮
The kennel won't take her.\nShe has crate anxiety.
你不可能這樣自私
You can't possibly\nbe this selfish.
對不起，親愛的，但劇院正在打電話給我
I'm sorry, honey, but the\ntheater is calling me.
（手機振動）
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
哦！字面意思他們需要我的衣服尺碼
Oh! Literally.\nThey need my dress size.
嗨，通常是零，但如果我臃腫，那就是兩個
Hi, there. Normally a zero,\nbut a two if I'm bloated.
晚安
Good night.
嘿，不要熬夜太晚
Hey, don't stay up too late.
凱特：哦，上帝
KATE: Oh, God.
undefined\n(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
undefined\n(GASPS)
undefined\nHoly crap.
undefined\nHere we are. I'll be\naround if you need me.
undefined\n(CELL PHONE RINGING)
undefined\n(SIGHS)
undefined\nGuess where I am?
undefined\nSome dude's yacht.
undefined\nYou little tramp.
undefined\n- I'm cleaning the carpets.\n- Oh.
undefined\nOh, my God. Theresa,\nlook at this bathroom.
undefined\nGod, I could live in here!
undefined\nOh.
undefined\nAnd they have candy.\nWho has candy in the bathroom?
undefined\n(GAGS)
undefined\nThat's not candy.
undefined\nYeah, because nobody has candy\nin the bathroom.
undefined\n- Oh, God.\n- Because it's a bathroom!
undefined\nOkay, come on, show me more.\nWait, wait, wait.
undefined\nIs that the guy?\nIs he married? He's cute.
undefined\nLEONARDO: And that's not even\na very good picture.
undefined\nHello, Theresa!
undefined\n- Oh, God.\n- Hi!
（INDISTINCT CHATTER）
By the way, she's single,\nand horny.
（喘氣）
Yeah, I'm so sorry.
哇靠
I'll get out of here.
如果你需要我，我們在這裡會很有勇氣
No, no, no. I should get up.\nBusy day.
（手機鈴聲）
I've got a lot of...\nWhew!
（SIGHS）
Really nothing to do.\n(CHUCKLES)
猜猜我在哪兒？
Colin, I'm ready for\nmy Bloody Mary. Yeah.
一些傢伙的遊艇
Mostly Mary. Yeah.
你這個小流浪漢
Well, now you know.
- 我正在打掃地毯 - 哦
I'm a grown man with\na tattoo on his butt.
哦，我的上帝特麗莎，看看這個浴室
Is that Speedy Gonzales?
天啊，我可以住在這裡！
Do you know another cartoon\nmouse with a sombrero?
哦
(IMITATING SPEEDY GONZALES\nSPEAKING SPANISH)
他們有糖果在浴室裡有糖果嗎？
(IN ENGLISH)\nI hate the pussycat.
（GAGS）
(CHUCKLES)
那不是糖果
Let me guess, you were, uh, a\nlittle tipsy when you got that?
是的，因為沒有人在浴室裡有糖果
Not at all.
- 哦，上帝 - 因為這是一間浴室！
I love Speedy.\nHe's fast, he's charming.
好的，來吧，告訴我更多等等，等等
He's Mexican.
是那個人嗎？他結婚了嗎？他很可愛
He outsmarts the pussycat
萊昂納多：這甚至都不是很好的畫面
and brings delicious\ncheese to his people.
你好，特麗莎！
And he's just fun to look at.
- 哦，天啊 - 嗨！
My name is Leonardo.
順便說一句，她是單身，而且是角質
Kate. Sullivan.
是的，我很抱歉
You're very attractive\nfor a carpet cleaning lady.
我會離開這裡
Yeah.
不，不，不，我應該起床
Although you maybe could do\nsomething with your hair.
我有很多哇！
Yeah...
真的無事可做（CHUCKLES）
No, well, no, that's not it.\nIt's your face.
科林，我準備好了血腥瑪麗呀
Yeah. I mean, it's good.
大多數瑪麗呀
I wanna like it,\nit's just...
好吧，現在你知道了
It's just somehow less than\nthe sum of its parts.
我是一個成年男子，他的屁股上有紋身
What animal do people\nsay you look like?
那是Speedy Gonzales嗎？
Apologies, sir, I thought\nyou were up and about already.
你知道另一個帶闊邊帽的卡通小屋嗎？
Ah, finally.\nIt's about time.
（模仿速度GONZALESSPEAK西班牙語）
Um, have Chef Gerard prepare\nbreakfast. Then, fire him.
（英文）我討厭貓咪
Of course, but perhaps we could\ngive him a few weeks' notice.
（笑）
His wife's expecting.
讓我猜一下，當你得到那個時，你是，呃，有點醉意？
But his food is boring.
一點也不
Absolutely.
我喜歡SpeedyHe很快，他很有魅力
There you are,\nsleepyhead. Hi.
他是墨西哥人
Well, this is awkward.\nWe're wearing the same thing.
他超過了貓咪
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
並為他的人民帶來美味
- Boop! Boop!\n- (GIGGLING)
他看起來很有趣
(IN ENGLISH)\nLead the way, girls!
我的名字是萊昂納多
Okay.
凱特蘇利文
Boop! Boop!
你對地毯清潔女士很有吸引力
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
是啊
Boop!
雖然你可能會對你的頭髮做一些事情
Oh, try to hurry. I'm pretty\nsure I'm gonna need the room.
是啊
(KNOCKING)
不，嗯，不，那不是它，這是你的臉
- MAN: Excuse me, Captain?\n- Yeah.
是的我的意思是，這很好
Checked the engine,\nyou're in luck.
我想要它，它只是
It's just the anti-siphon\nvalve. No problem.
它只是在某種程度上減少了其各部分的總和
(SPEAKING NORWEGIAN)
人們看起來像什麼動物？
(IN ENGLISH)\nI was just telling him
道歉，先生，我雖然已經開始了
that I was right,\nand that he's a dumbass.
啊，終於是時候了
Say, how'd this dude\nmake all his money, anyway?
嗯，廚師Gerard準備好了然後，解雇他
He didn't.
當然，也許我們可以在幾周前通知他
His family owns the largest building\nsupply company in the world.
他妻子的期待
Now this is what\nhe does all day.
但他的食物很無聊
(GIRLS CHATTERING)
絕對
MECHANIC: Chicken fight?
你有，睡覺嗨
(R&B MUSIC PLAYING)
嗯，這很尷尬我們穿著同樣的東西
(CAR HORN HONKS)
（講西班牙語）
(MAGDALENA SPEAKING SPANISH)
-  Boop！Boop！ - （GIGGLING）
(FORCED LAUGHTER)
（英文）帶路，女孩們！
CAPTAIN: (IN ENGLISH)\nAll right. Here's my info.
好的
If you're ever in Norway,\nlook me up.
布普！布普！
The summers are insane.
（GIRLS GIGGLING）
That's happening, Oddvar.\nThat's definitely happening.
布普！
Hi. Excuse me, I was\ntold to clean in there.
哦，試著快點我好意思，我需要房間
Something about\na glitter bomb?
（敲）
Is that gonna disturb you?
- 男：對不起，船長？ - 是的
No, not at all.
檢查發動機，你很幸運
Hmm. I'm craving something.\nWhat is it?
這只是反虹吸閥沒問題
(SMACKS LIPS)
（演講挪威人）
Excuse me,\nare you talking to me?
（英文）我只是告訴他
Sweet, but not\ntoo sweet. Hmm.
我是對的，他是個笨蛋
Is it mango? I'm pretty\nsure it's mango.
說，無論如何，這個花錢怎麼樣？
No. No, wait, wait.\nIt's papaya.
他沒有
Is it papaya?
他的家族擁有世界上最大的建築供應公司
I would have no way\nof knowing that.
現在這就是我整天都在做的事情
(SCOFFS) Of course.
（GIRLS CHATTERING）
Could you be a doll\nand get me a little of both?
機械：雞鬥？
Hmm?
（R
You know I was just hired\nto do carpets, right?
我不明白為什麼這會阻止你給我一點零食
I don't see why that should prevent\nyou from getting me a little snack.
難道你沒有，像其他10,000個人那樣為你做這件事嗎？
Don't you have, like, 10,000\nother people to do that for you?
是的但你就在這裡
Yeah. But you're right here.
好的，我很抱歉，但我真的要完成了
Okay, I'm sorry, but I really\nhave to finish up
所以我可以從學校挑選我的女生
so I can pick my girls\nup from school.
（查克斯）噓
(CHUCKLES) Shh.
（西班牙語中的混蛋）
(MUTTERING IN SPANISH)
（英文）也許你不知道我是誰
(IN ENGLISH) Perhaps\nyou don't know who I am.
我確切地知道你是誰
I know exactly who you are.
你告訴我你的屁股和我的自尊心
You showed me your ass and did\na number on my self-esteem.
那我為什麼不吃水果？
Then why don't\nI have my fruit?
打敗我，但我沒有得到它
Beats me.\nBut I'm not getting it.
好的很公平
Okay. Fair enough.
你被開除了
You're fired.
（喘氣）
(GASPS)
為了不給你一個芒果？
For not getting you a mango?
還是木瓜
Or a papaya.
好的，你知道嗎？沒關係
Okay, you know what?\nThat's fine.
只要付錢給我，我就會在路上
Just pay me\nand I'll be on my way.
（笑）
(CHUCKLES)
我不付給你或“WeCare地毯和面料公司”
I'm not paying you or the "We\nCare Carpet and Fabric Company."
夥計，你那裡有廁所
Dude, you have\na toilet in there
這比一年的成本高
that costs more than\nI make in a year.
你聘請我去做一份工作我這樣做你付錢給我了
You hired me to do a job.\nI did it. You're paying me.
不
Nope.
黑山先生，隨時準備出貨
Mr. Montenegro, ready\nto ship out when you are.
太棒了！推開太平洋等待
Great! Push off.\nThe Pacific awaits.
再見，凱特
Goodbye, Kate.
（驚歎）
(EXCLAIMS)
你是一個可怕的人
You are a horrible person.
一流的混蛋！
A first-class asshole!
“一流的混蛋”
"A first-class asshole."
你自己不是有魅力的人
You're no charmer yourself.
哦，哇！那蜇了
Oh, whoa! That stung.
（笑）
(LAUGHING)
你自私，居高臨下！
You selfish,\ncondescending prick!
我打賭你在整個自我吸收的生活中沒有工作過一天
I bet you haven't worked a single day\nin your entire, self-absorbed life.
（說其他語言）
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
（笑）
(LAUGHING)
並且認為我很想，這很接近，
And to think I was\nthis, this close,
邀請你加入按摩浴缸
to inviting you to join\nus in the Jacuzzi.
（嘲笑）
(SCOFFS)
世界上沒有足夠的青黴素！
There isn't enough\npenicillin in the world!
（HONKS）
(HONKS)
不，不，等等，不，不
No, no, wait.\nNo, no, no.
不要不要解開船
No. Don't untie the boat.
對不起，請原諒！上尉！我還在船上
Excuse me, wait. Excuse me!\nCaptain! I'm still on board.
- 不要離開！ - （音樂播放）
- Don't leave yet!\n- (LOUD MUSIC PLAYING)
女人崇拜我，我很迷人，健康，無病
Women adore me. I'm charming,\nand fit, and disease-free.
哦，長大了
Oh, grow up.
你是一個虛榮，空虛的小男人，
You are a vain,\nempty little man,
除了他爸爸的錢，他什麼都不是
who'd be nothing\nwithout his daddy's money.
（笑）
(LAUGHS)
凱特：哦，不！
KATE: Oh, no!
你一定是在開玩笑吧！哇，哇，哇！等等
You gotta be kidding me!\nWhoa, whoa, whoa! Wait.
跳得更好
Better jump off.
不，不，我不會去任何地方，直到你，
No. No. I am not going\nanywhere, until you,
或者你的一個butlersor bimbos給我寫了一張支票
or one of your butlers\nor bimbos writes me a check.
好下一站，三藩市
Fine. Next stop,\nSan Francisco.
好吧，接下來的12個小時裡，我會很痛苦
Fine. I'll be a pain in your\nass for the next 12 hours.
（SIGHS）
(SIGHS)
我想我沒想過這個
I guess I didn't\nthink this through.
不，你沒有
No, you didn't.
我無法相信你讓我這樣做
I can't believe\nyou're making me do this.
（慘叫）
(SCREAMS)
（喘氣）
(GASPING)
你到底怎麼了？
What the hell\nis wrong with you?
等等！我的設備
Wait! My equipment.
LEONARDO：哦，當然
LEONARDO: Oh, of course.
這個給你
Here you are.
不！不，不，不！這是非常昂貴的！不！
No! No, no, no!\nIt's very expensive! No!
哦!
Oh!
等我忘了你的東西
Wait. I forgot something.\nYour bucket.
- 取指 - 不！
- Fetch.\n- No!
（LEONARDO LAUGHS）
(LEONARDO LAUGHS)
（音樂播放）
(LOUD MUSIC PLAYING)
LEONARDO：你知道的，
LEONARDO:\nAnd just so you know,
我的生活並不空虛！嗯？
my life is not empty!\nHmm?
每個人都希望我的生活因為它有意義
Everyone wants my life\nbecause it's meaningful.
我恨你！
I hate you!
再見
Goodbye.
（叫聲）
(GRUNTING)
（LEONARDO LAUGHS）
(LEONARDO LAUGHS)
（SIGHS）
(SIGHS)
天啊
Oh, God.
而現在我欠清潔公司3000美元的新機器！
And now I owe the cleaning company\n$3,000 for a new machine!
他們解雇了我，他是魔鬼
And they fired me.\nHe is the devil.
哇，誰是魔鬼？
Whoa, who's the devil?
- 萊昂納多黑山 - 誰是那個？
- Leonardo Montenegro.\n- Who's that?
在這裡說他是世界上第三富翁的兒子
Says here he's the son of the\nthird richest man in the world.
一個拉丁美洲人？地獄耶，是天才，寶貝，showin'up
A Latino? Hell yeah.\nMi gente, babe, showin' up.
嘿！這些是給船員的，對嗎？不是他們的老闆？
Hey! Those are for the crew,\nright? Not their boss?
你在說什麼，寶貝？我減掉了八磅
What are you talking about,\nbabe? I lost eight pounds.
很快，我要打破我的緊身襯衫
Pretty soon I'm gonna be\nbreaking out my skinny shirts.
（發聲）
(VOCALIZING)
我喜歡他跳舞的時候
I love when he dances.
帶回哈塞爾貝克
Bring back the Hasselbeck.
凱特：你知道我在銀行帳戶裡得到了什麼嗎？
KATE: You know what I got\nin my bank account?
42美元我今晚需要得到另一份工作
$42. I need to get\nanother job. Like, tonight.
鮑比，你在招人嗎？
Bobby, are you hiring?
是的，當然，如果你整天可以提供混凝土袋
Yeah, sure, if you can haul\ngiant bags of concrete all day.
我們可能會為你籌集幾塊錢
We could probably scrape\ntogether a few bucks for you.
Just Benny開始上大學，有人買了船！
Just Benny started college\nand somebody bought a boat!
來吧，寶貝，我們要搬運這個？
Come on, babe,\nwe're gonna relitigate this?
我為這艘船付出了相當大的代價
I paid significantly\nbelow market for that boat.
我不得不買它這是一個偷
I had to buy it.\nIt was a steal.
為什麼我甚至想成為一名護士？
Why am I even trying\nto be a nurse?
我要去披薩
I'm gonna be\ndelivering pizzas
在我的餘生中清潔地毯
and cleaning carpets\nfor the rest of my life.
凱特，別說嘿，看
Kate, don't say that.\nHey, look.
有一個大蒜結
Have a garlic knot.
我保證，它會使一切變得更好
It makes everything just a\nlittle bit better, I promise.
不，它沒有
No, it doesn't.
不，我會有一個
No? I'll have one.
（UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING）
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
評論員：更多的回到中場，
COMMENTATOR: Moretti\nplays it back to midfield,
一如既往地控制空間
controlling the\npace as always.
（笑）
(LAUGHS)
（講法語）
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
（呻吟）
(MOANING)
哎呀
Oops.
（英文）給我第二個不要轉過來
(IN ENGLISH) Give me a second.\nDon't turn of.
（講法語）
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
（英文）我的安全套抽屜是空的
(IN ENGLISH)\nMy condom drawer's empty.
我會解決這個問題
I'll fix this.
門敞開著，但馬格努松猶豫不決
And the door was wide open,\nbut Magnusson hesitates...
（電話響鈴）
(PHONE RINGING)
我一再告訴那個男人，
I've told\nthe man repeatedly,
九分鐘我正在吃晚飯，
for the nine minutes\nI am having my supper,
我不在
I am off the clock.
（電視音量增加）
(TV VOLUME INCREASES)
我付給這些人的是什麼？
What am I paying\nthese people for?
- 我會回來的 - 好的
- I'll be back.\n- Okay.
（講法語）
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
- （WHOOPS） - （CHUCKLES）
- (WHOOPS)\n- (CHUCKLES)
（喘氣）
(GASPS)
（笑著）
(CHUCKLING)
（嗡嗡）
(HUMMING)
（英文）請在這裡
(IN ENGLISH)\nPlease be here.
（SCOFFS）該死的，我是無情的
(SCOFFS) Damn it,\nI'm relentless.
嗯
Hmm.
- （UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING） - （唱歌）
- (UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)\n- (SINGING ALONG)
（笑）
(LAUGHS)
是!
Yes!
五！
Five!
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
（LEONARDO WHOOPING）
(LEONARDO WHOOPING)
（發聲）
(VOCALIZING)
哇！
Whoa!
（英文）幫助我，有人！
(IN ENGLISH)\nHelp me, somebody!
請幫幫我！
Help me, please!
請，任何人，幫助！
Please, anyone, help!
科林！救命啊！
Colin! Help!
- 目標！ - 所有：是的！是的！
- Goal!\n- ALL: Yeah! Yeah!
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
（英文）幫助我！
(IN ENGLISH) Help me!
（英文）幫助，船長！
(IN ENGLISH) Help, Captain!
（音樂續表）
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
（尖叫）
(SCREAMING)
（水上飛濺）
(WATER SPLASHES)
（英文呼喊）幫助！幫助，有人！
(SHOUTS IN ENGLISH)\nHelp! Help, somebody!
（呻吟聲）
(GROANS)
（INDISTINCT CHATTER）
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
謝菲爾德：粗暴的夜晚，朋友？
SHERIFF: Rough night, pal?
嘿!
Hey!
（SIREN WAILS）
(SIREN WAILS)
女士，我不想讓希望更加美好。
I don't wanna get\nyour hopes up, ma'am,
但我們可能找到了他
but we might\nhave found him.
LEONARDO：就像我告訴官員一樣
LEONARDO:\nLike I told the officer,
我不知道今天是哪一天我不知道我出生在哪裡
I don't know what day it is.\nI don't know where I was born.
我甚至都不知道自己的名字
I don't even know my own name.
我記得不是醒來，而是醒來
I remember nothing\nexcept waking up
在沙灘上，充滿了沙子的屁股
on a beach with\nan ass full of sand.
你是醫生，對吧？
You're a doctor, right?
好吧，解決它
Well, fix it.
並且
And also...
（WHISPERING）我可以得到一個更漂亮的護士嗎？
(WHISPERING)\nCan I get a prettier nurse?
她很漂亮
She is the pretty one.
醫生：可能由內側顳葉的急性創傷引起
DOCTOR: Probably caused by acute\ntrauma to the medial temporal lobe.
失憶症，真的嗎？它是永久性的嗎？
Amnesia, really?\nIs it permanent?
嗯，腦力是一件棘手的事情
Well, the brain\nis a tricky thing.
他可能會在幾天後回憶起他的記憶
He might get his memory back\nin a couple of days
或者根本不可能
or maybe never at all.
但說實話，我們只有
But to be honest,\nwe've only had
在Elk Cove的一例失憶症
one case of amnesia\nhere in Elk Cove
那是80年代的年輕女性
and that was a pretty young\nwoman back in the '80s.
手指交叉，這是你的兄弟，
Fingers crossed,\nthis is your brother,
但這是一個海濱小鎮，我們在這裡分享無家可歸者
but this is a beach town, we do\nget our share of homeless here.
那麼，如果他只是住在街上的那些人，會發生什麼呢？
So what happens if he's just some\npoor guy living on the street?
然後他將被送往賽勒姆的一個精神病院
Then he'll be shipped off to a\npsychiatric facility up in Salem.
- 哦，我的上帝 - 人們迷失在那裡
- Oh, my God.\n- People get lost up there.
我們到了
Here we are.
而他真的沒有什麼？
And he really\nremembers nothing?
不是一件事
Not a thing.
LEONARDO：第一百次，我不想吃雞肉或牛肉
LEONARDO: For the hundredth time,\nI don't want chicken or beef.
我想要魚
I want fish.
一塊簡單的烤海鱸魚配黃油霞多麗
A simple, grilled piece of sea bass.\nWith a buttery Chardonnay.
（嗚咽）那不是我的兄弟
(WHISPERING)\nThat's not my brother.
LEONARDO：做吧！今天！
LEONARDO: Do it! Today!
你在等什麼？
What are you waiting for?
（LEONARDO說西班牙語）
(LEONARDO SPEAKING SPANISH)
媽的
Oh, shit.
媽的！嗷
Shit! Ow.
拉屎！
Shit!
拉屎
Shit.
我有兩個星期我有一個完全焦慮的攻擊
I got two weeks. I am having\na total anxiety attack.
我不能讓女孩再次移動
I can't make\nthose girls move again.
好的，親愛的，我在我的錢包裡拿了半個Xanax
Okay, honey, hang on. I got\na half a Xanax in my purse.
我們要把它搞定
We're gonna\nfigure this out.
凱特看看這個
Kate. Look at this.
我在Beachcomber尋找一台二手割草機，看看我發現了什麼
I was searching for a used lawnmower in\nthe Beachcomber, and look what I found.
失憶症就在這裡我們的小鎮
Amnesia. Right here\nin our little town.
我告訴過你，這些東西一直都在發生
I told you this stuff happens\nall the time.
杜德不知道他是誰
Dude has no idea who he is.
哦，我的上帝
Oh, my God.
哦，我的上帝就是他
Oh, my God.\nThat's him.
那是混蛋！（GASPS）
That's the asshole!\n(GASPS)
“一個身份不明的無家可歸者
"An unidentified homeless man.
“一般逆行性健忘症
"General retrograde amnesia.
“希望墨西哥城的女人
"There was hope\na Mexico City woman
“附近的遊艇可能是他的妹妹，但是”
"yachting nearby\nmight be his sister, but..."
那是他的妹妹（SCOFFS）
That was his sister.\n(SCOFFS)
難以置信的
Unbelievable.
我打賭她假裝不認識他，
I bet she's pretending\nnot to know him,
所以她可以超越公司
so she can take over\nthe company.
他們在Amm Sin Maquillaje上做到了這一點
They did that on\nAmor sin Maquillaje.
好的
Okay.
我們現在要去醫院了
We are going down\nto the hospital right now
得到錢我欠我的錢
and getting the money\nhe owes me.
並為痛苦和痛苦增添一點點
And add a little\nfor pain and suffering, too.
哦，是的，我會添加很多他像對待我一樣對待我
Oh, yeah. I'm gonna add a lot.\nHe treated me like crap.
是的，還有新的夾板
Yeah, and I\nneed new cleats.
我們都是gonnaget新的夾板！
We're all gonna\nget new cleats!
THERESA：好的，等等，凱特？
THERESA: Okay, wait.\nHey, Kate?
如果他知道你是誰，他就不付錢給你，
If he didn't pay you when\nhe knew who you were,
是什麼讓你認為他現在會付錢給你？
what makes you think\nhe's gonna pay you now?
（GROWLS）這太令人沮喪了！
(GROWLS)\nThis is so frustrating!
我討厭有錢人他們逃避一切
I hate rich people.\nThey get away with everything.
但你知道嗎？不，這次不是
But you know what?\nNo, not this time.
因為我不是gonnatell他們是誰
Because I am not gonna\ntell them who he is.
我只是想讓他在那裡
I am just gonna let him\nrot in there.
是的，你可以這樣做，
Yeah, you could do that,
或者你可以像他們一樣，並利用這種情況
or you can be like them and take\nadvantage of the situation.
怎麼樣？我怎麼能這樣做？
How? How could I do that?
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
（英文）什麼？（說西班牙語）
(IN ENGLISH) What?\n(SPEAKING SPANISH)
（SIGHS）
(SIGHS)
（英文）州或聯邦？
(IN ENGLISH)\nState or federal?
THERESA：好吧，嘿，女孩們我需要你?明你的媽媽
THERESA: All right, hey, girls. I'm\ngonna need you to help your mom
挖出一些舊的家庭照片
dig up some old family photos.
我要請鮑比借給我們一盒他無用的，瘦小的衣服，
I'm gonna ask Bobby to loan us a box\nof his useless, skinny clothes,
因為我有一個你會討厭的想法，
because I have an idea\nthat you're gonna hate,
但你錯了，因為它的正義是詩意的
but you're wrong because\nit is poetic in its justice.
- 凱特：你好
- KATE: Hi.\n- Hi.
我來這裡接我的丈夫，那個失憶症的男人
I'm here to pick up my\nhusband, the man with amnesia.
哦，你一定是凱特？
Oh. You must be Kate?
弗萊徹博士很高興接到你的電話
Dr. Fletcher was so excited\nto get your call.
我們都是
We all were.
我會去找他的
I'll go get him.
幾乎忘了這裡他和他在一起的一切
Almost forgot. Here's\neverything he had with him.
謝謝
Thank you.
等等，好吧，你只是緊張
Wait, okay,\nyou're just nervous.
是的，真的很緊張
Yeah, really nervous.
這很瘋狂，可能是非法的
This is crazy\nand probably illegal.
凱特，來吧你去哪了？
Kate, come on.\nWhere are you going?
看，你想被驅逐嗎？
Look, do you wanna get evicted?
當然不是
Of course not.
好吧，那麼，堅持腳本我們有一個計畫
Okay, well, then stick to the script.\nWe have a plan.
一個月，testBobby將雇用他，
One month until the test.\nBobby will hire him,
而他將是一個額外的薪水，所以你有時間學習
and he'll be an extra paycheck,\nso you have time to study.
我幾乎不知道那個人我不會讓他搬進去
I barely know the guy.\nI am not gonna let him move in.
但是你在那裡學習，學習
But you're gonna\nbe there, studying.
這就是為什麼它是天才
That's why it's genius.
他永遠不會和孩子們一起獨鬥
He'll never have to be\nalone with the kids.
來吧
Come on.
你正在為你的女孩做這件事
You're doing this\nfor your girls.
我正在為我的女孩這樣做
I'm doing this for my girls.
你去吧
There you go.
好的，在這裡，使用thisBobby甚至都不會注意到
Okay, here, use this.\nBobby won't even notice.
好消息
Good news.
你的妻子來帶你回家
Your wife has come\nto take you home.
（SCOFFS）最後是關於時間的
(SCOFFS) Finally.\nIt's about time.
什麼？等待
What? Wait.
我結婚了？
I'm married?
嗨，親愛的
Hi, honey.
我不認識這位元女士
I do not recognize this lady.
（SIGHS）我擔心這會發生
(SIGHS) I was afraid\nthis would happen.
你帶來了我們談過的材料嗎？
Did you bring the materials\nwe talked about?
我知道這一定非常迷惑，
I know this must be\nvery disorienting,
但這是我們的婚姻許可證
but here's our\nmarriage license.
我叫Leo Sullivan？
My name is Leo Sullivan?
是你的曾祖父
Yes. Your great-grandfather...
你曾曾的曾祖父Finbar Sullivan，
Your great-great-grandfather,\nFinbar Sullivan,
從愛爾蘭移民到1846年的戰爭中為墨西哥而戰
emigrated from Ireland, to fight\nfor Mexico in the war of 1846.
（SMACKS LIPS）
(SMACKS LIPS)
那是gobbledygook！這不可能是真的
That's gobbledygook!\nIt can't be true.
親愛的，我們已經結婚15年了
Honey, we have been\nmarried for 15 years.
我們有三個很好的女兒
We have three\nwonderful daughters.
不，我沒有辦法生孩子
No, there's no way\nI have children.
如果我這樣做，他們就會成為兒子
And if I did,\nthey'd be sons.
我只是說
I'm just saying.
我有你的護照，你的出生證明
I have your passport,\nyour birth certificate...
哦
Oh...
這是我們蜜月的照片
Here's a photo\nfrom our honeymoon.
我們去了里諾？
We went to Reno?
現在我知道你在說謊
Now I know you're lying.
Leo！親愛的，別說不解
Leo! Sweetie,\nstop puzzling.
我很困惑
I'm puzzling.
你和我是我和Leo Sullivan夫人
You and I are\nMr. and Mrs. Leo Sullivan.
我們在坎昆會面
We met in Cancun.
你是一名導遊
You were a tour guide.
我在遊輪上工作
I was working\non a cruise ship.
這個響鈴是什麼？
Is any of this\nringing a bell?
沒什麼
Nope. Nothing.
我每次停靠時都會約會
We dated\nevery time I docked.
我們會得到優酪乳
We would get\nfrozen yogurt
並觀看Playa Tortugas的日光浴
and watch the sunset\nover the Playa Tortugas.
那就是我們墜入愛河的地方
That's where\nwe fell in love.
聽起來像是浪漫，獅子座
Sounds like you're\na romantic, Leo.
（SIGHS）看，看，看
(SIGHS) Look, look, look.
我承認有很多事情我已經忘記了，
I admit there are many things\nI've forgotten,
但是從我靈魂的深處，
but from the depths\nof my soul,
我知道我沒和這個女人結婚
I know I'm not married\nto this woman.
所以，除非我看到真實的證據，
So, unless I see\nsome real proof,
我在自助餐廳吃了一塊餡餅，嗯？
I'm getting a slice\nof pie at the cafeteria, hmm?
祝你好運，瘋狂的女士
Good luck, crazy lady.
等等，等等蜂蜜？
Wait, wait. Wait. Honey?
我不想這樣說，
I didn't wanna say this,
因為我知道你很尷尬
because I know\nit embarrasses you.
但你右邊的臉頰上有一個卡通滑鼠的紋身
But you have a tattoo of a cartoon\nmouse on your right butt cheek.
不，我沒有
No, I don't.
你真的是我的妻子？
You're really my wife?
無論好壞，寶貝
For better or worse, baby.
好的，我們在這裡
All right, here we are.
我知道它看起來不像，但它充滿了愛
I know it doesn't look like\nmuch, but it's full of love.
我很窮？
I'm poor?
對
Yup.
進來
Come on in.
哦，爸爸！
Oh, Dad!
- 爸爸！ - 我們非常想念你
- Daddy!\n- We missed you so much.
（狗狗隊）
(DOG BARKS)
我很高興你沒事
I'm so glad you're okay.
艾米麗？
Emily?
嘿
Hey.
她太酷了，不能承認，
She's too cool to admit it,
但她最擔心的是所有人
but she was\nthe most worried of all.
（STAMMERING）對不起，我不認識你們
(STAMMERING) I'm sorry, I\ndon't recognize any of you.
哦，來吧
Oh, come on.
莫莉，奧利維亞，艾米莉，
Molly, Olivia, Emily,
你的三個火槍手？
your three musketeers?
沒有
No.
呃我有作業
Uh... I've got homework.
他們怎麼不像我一樣？
How come they don't\nlook like me?
哦，親愛的
Oh, sweetie...
我們遇到了麻煩，
We had trouble\ngetting pregnant,
所以我們不得不使用精子供體
so we had to use\na sperm donor.
我不育了？
I'm sterile?
這不會改變一件事
That doesn't change a thing.
你還是他們的父親
You are still their father.
你為這個家庭做了一切
You've done everything\nfor this family.
採取兩個，甚至三個工作
Taken two, even three jobs.
我工作？
I work?
你覺得我們怎麼能為這一切付出代價？
How do you think\nwe can pay for all of this?
我不敢問，但我該怎麼做才能謀生？
I'm afraid to ask, but\nwhat do I do for a living?
好吧，在你下崗之前，
Well, before\nyou got laid off,
你是家禽加工廠的工頭
you were a foreman at\nthe poultry processing plant.
幸運的是，鮑比，
Luckily, Bobby,
老闆的老公，你見過保齡球，
my boss's husband,\nyou met bowling,
給了他一家建築公司的工作
gave you a job\nat his construction company.
我知道，這是糟糕的，艱苦的工作
It is awful, backbreaking\nwork, I know,
但我們很幸運能擁有它
but we are lucky\nto have it.
（SIGHS）
(SIGHS)
我需要喝很多酒
I need a drink.\nLots of them.
- （CHUCKLES） - 什麼？請不要告訴我我很清醒？
- (CHUCKLES)\n- What? Please don't tell me I'm sober?
你有三年籌碼，
You had your three-year chip,
但是你復發了
but then you relapsed
而你最終在那個海灘上
and you ended up on that beach.
那是什麼？四天？你有四天，親愛的
So what is that? Four days?\nYou got four days, honey.
- 我們仍為你感到驕傲 - 嗯嗯
- We're still really proud of you.\n- Mm-hmm.
我懂了
I see.
沒有酒精
No alcohol. Whatsoever.
納達
Nada.
我需要使用洗手間
I need to use the restroom.
我認為那是帶廁所的房間
I assume it's that room\nover there with the toilet.
看著你，寶貝一切都回來了！
Look at you, babe.\nIt's all coming back!
（笑）
(CHUCKLES)
布普
Boop.
我不喜歡那樣
I don't like that.
（石鱸）
(GRUNTS)
多一個
One more.
Boop，boop！（YOWLS）
Boop, boop! (YOWLS)
這不可能是我的生活
This can't be my life.
（SIGHS）
(SIGHS)
蜜糖！
Honey!
- 哎嗨
- Hey!\n- Hi.
在衛生紙上跑得很低
Running low on toilet paper.
在水槽下！
Under the sink!
當然
Of course.
（CHUCKLING）是的
(CHUCKLING) Yes.
當然，在水槽下麵
Under the sink,\nof course.
請把我親愛的兄弟留在你的祈禱中
Please keep my beloved brother\nin your prayers
當你回到墨西哥
as you head back to Mexico.
我會留在這裡直到我找到他
I'm going to stay here\nuntil I find him.
活著還是
Alive or...
好心思，人們只有善意
Good thoughts, people.\nOnly good thoughts.
我胖了？
I was fat?
嗯，是的你喝酒時沒有做出最好的決定，親愛的
Um, yeah. You didn't make the best\ndecisions when you were drinking, honey.
（WHISPERING）明天我們要去見善意
(WHISPERING) Tomorrow\nwe're going to Goodwill.
鮑比的緊身衣服不瘦
Bobby's skinny clothes\nare not skinny.
我認為這些海鷹隊是一種運動隊
I assume these Seahawks\nare some kind of sports team
我是個粉絲，
and I'm a big fan,
因為我的衣服很多
because most of my clothes
它上面有這種神奇的綠色和藍色的鳥
have this God-awful\ngreen and blue bird on it.
足球，爸爸是我們的事
Football, Dad.\nIt's our thing.
我們一起觀看每場比賽
We watch every game together.
即使我沒有完成我的作業
Even when I haven't\ndone my homework.
嘿每個人都做家庭作業
Hey. Everyone does\ntheir homework.
包括我和現在我已經準備好了胸外科手術的協議
Including me. And right now I've gotta\nmemorize protocols for thoracic surgery.
所以，獅子座，你為什麼不開始玩耍？
So, Leo, why don't you get\ndinner started?
什麼？做飯？我？庫克？
What? Cook? Me? Cook?
親愛的，我知道你有頭部受傷，
Sweetheart, I know\nyou had a head injury,
但我們達成了協定
but we made a deal.
我正在攻讀考試，
While I'm studying for my exam,
你讓房子繼續運轉
you keep the house running.
但我甚至不知道怎麼打開爐子
But I don't even know\nhow to turn on the stove.
哦，親愛的，來吧
Oh! Honey, come on.
沙拉，義大利面冰箱裡有一罐醬汁
Salad, pasta. There's a jar\nof sauce in the fridge.
天啊
Holy cow.
哦，哦，哦，呃，原諒我
Ooh, ooh, ooh,\nuh, pardon me.
溫暖的一天，沒有什麼比冰冷的啤酒更好的了
Nothing like an icy cold beer\non a warm day.
嗯，嗯
Mmm, mmm.
（EXHALES）是的
(EXHALES) Yes.
（INDISTINCT CHATTER）
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
啊!
Ugh!
這是我們總是使用的醬油嗎？
Is this the sauce\nwe always use?
它的味道就像紅色一樣
It tastes like red nothing.
當面條完成後你怎麼說？
And how are you supposed to tell\nwhen the noodles are done?
品嘗一個
Taste one.
（柔軟地塗抹）
(GROANING SOFTLY)
嗯嗯
Mmm. Mmm.
熱熱熱！
Hot, hot, hot!
什麼時候女僕來了？
When's the maid coming?
正如我所說，我擔心我是女僕
As I'm saying this,\nI fear I'm the maid.
親愛的，沒有人像你那樣清潔
No one cleans\nlike you do, sweetie.
（石鱸）
(GRUNTS)
（WHISPERS）這太棒了
(WHISPERS) This is awesome.
凱特：親愛的？
KATE: Honey?
儘量不要稀釋我們都非常饑餓
Try not to dilly dally.\nWe're all super hungry.
我喜歡有個爸爸
I like having a dad around.
他不是你的父親，天才
He's not your dad, genius.
你同意有一個好的態度
You agreed to have\na good attitude.
如果你讓他照看孩子，我會有一個很好的態度，
And I'll have a great attitude\nif you let him babysit,
所以我不會一直在這裡看著這些傢伙
so I'm not stuck here watching\nthese guys all the time.
我們過去了，我不想讓他照看孩子
We went over this.\nI don't want him to babysit.
為什麼他只做你的家務？
Why does he only get\nto do your chores?
我想像我班上的其他孩子一樣去游泳池
I wanna go to the pool like\nevery other kid in my class.
我不在乎！他不是保姆
I don't care!\nHe's not babysitting.
因為你認為他是變態？
'Cause you think\nhe's a pervert?
當然不是！
Of course not!
什麼是變態？
What's a pervert?
- 沒什麼 - 那我可以買一個嗎？
- Nothing.\n- Then can I have one?
不！他不是保姆和故事
No! He's not babysitting.\nEnd of story.
晚安
Good night.
奧利維亞：我什麼都沒得到
OLIVIA: I never get anything.
那麼，這是魔術發生的地方嗎？
So, is this where\nthe magic happens?
你甚至不記得我是誰，
You don't even remember\nwho I am,
你還想和我做愛嗎？
and you still wanna\nhave sex with me?
是的非常多
Yes. Very much.
基本上，
So, basically,
你想和一個完全陌生的人發生性關係嗎？
you wanna have sex\nwith a complete stranger?
是的非常多
Yes. Very much.
好吧，大男孩
All right, big boy.
你知道規則
You know the rules.
什麼？嘿，等等，等等
What? Hey, wait, wait, wait.
我不跟你睡覺？
I'm not sleeping with you?
你需要30天清潔和清醒
You need 30 days\nclean and sober.
你和你的贊助商提出了這個想法，而不是我的想法
You and your sponsor came up with that.\nIt was your idea, not mine.
（STAMMERS）你在說什麼？
(STAMMERS)\nWhat are you saying?
- 噓！ - 你要讓我睡在沙發上？
- Boop!\n- You're gonna make me sleep on the couch?
不，我們上次嘗試過
Nope. We tried that last time
你最後在酒櫃裡走了
and you ended up\nin the liquor cabinet.
（嘲笑）
(SCOFFS)
那麼，我在哪裡睡覺？
So, where am I sleeping?
幹得好
Here you go.
你有一張嬰兒床和一切
You have a cot and everything.
好吧，
All right,
所以我要把房子鎖起來過夜
so I'm gonna lock up\nthe house for the night.
如果你需要使用浴室，
If you need to use the bathroom,
幹得好
here you go.
我不是人
I'm a nobody.
一個貧窮，無菌，醉酒的人，
A poor, sterile, drunk nobody,
誰必須在瓶子裡撒尿
who has to pee in a bottle.
但你是我的無人
But you're my nobody.
好吧，鮑比在早上接你，明亮而早
All right, Bobby's picking you up\nin the morning, bright and early.
所以你需要休息一下，好嗎？
So you need to get\nsome rest, okay?
哦，小心熊
Oh, and watch out for bears.
- （鬧鐘響鈴） - （LEONARDO SCREAMING）
- (ALARM CLOCK RINGING)\n- (LEONARDO SCREAMING)
（打哈欠）
(YAWNS)
- （無線電的INDISTINCT CHATTER） - 布宜諾賽勒斯
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO)\n- Buenos dias.
- 漂亮的襯衫 - 謝謝
- Nice shirt.\n- Thank you.
是的，不要灑上它
Yeah, don't spill on it.
這是一個經典和一切
It's a classic and everything.
說真的，他們很難找到
Seriously, they're hard to find.
BOBBY：好的，大家好
BOBBY: Okay, everybody.
這是獅子座
This is Leo.
Burro Burrito\nBurro. Burrito.
維托，因為他愛教父
Vito, because he loves\nThe Godfather.
這是我毫無價值的侄子，傑森
This is my worthless nephew,\nJason.
我們稱他為幸運，因為他很幸運能找到一份工作
We call him Lucky, because\nhe's lucky to have a job.
而且因為我受到了兩次真實的打擊
And 'cause I got hit by\nlightning. Twice. For real.
我甚至不應該在這裡
I shouldn't even be here.
Yeah Gordo就像是，“哇，狗屎！”
Yeah. Gordo was like,\n"Whoa, shit!"
兄弟，你不要打電話給我，好嗎？
Bro, you don't get\nto call me that, okay?
並且不要那麼自大我以前看起來就像你一樣
And don't be so cocky.\nI used to look just like you.
頭髮，腹肌，小臥室的眼睛
The hair, the abs,\nthe little bedroom eyes.
你絕對不會打電話給我
You definitely don't\nget to call me that.
- 你必須為我工作至少六個月，好嗎？ - （講西班牙語）
- You gotta work for me at least six months, okay?\n- (SPEAKS SPANISH)
（英文）來吧，我們有一個游泳池去挖掘讓我們走吧
(IN ENGLISH) Come on, we got\na pool to dig. Let's go.
（笑聲）
(LAUGHTER)
嘿
Hey.
聽著，我很確定我從未工作過
Listen, I'm pretty sure\nI've never worked construction.
所以，我可能更適合跑腿，
So, I might be more suited\nfor running errands,
或者可能是輕鬆的辦公室工作
or maybe\nsome light office work.
我可以成為獲得松餅的人
I could be the guy\nwho gets the muffins.
看，我退後了，好嗎？
Look, I got your back,\nall right?
- 我會對你很輕鬆 - 很好
- I'll go easy on you.\n- Good.
- 很棒 - （講西班牙語）
- Great.\n- (SPEAKING SPANISH)
（叫聲）
(GRUNTING)
BOBBY：喲！
BOBBY: Yo!
這有什麼慢慢記憶，Lady Hands？
Any of this jogging your memory,\nLady Hands?
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
（笑）
(LAUGHING)
（英文）在此之後，我找到了一份非常輕鬆的工作
(IN ENGLISH) After this I got\na real easy job for you.
不，我只是在開玩笑，兄弟
No, I'm just kidding, bro.
（笑）
(LAUGHING)
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
（嗅探）
(SNIFFING)
- （SNIFFLING） - 呃
- (SNIFFLING)\n- Uh...
不不不
No, no, no.
（兩個人）
(BOTH SOBBING)
（叫聲）
(GRUNTING)
- 咖啡 - 是的
- Coffee.\n- Yes.
謝謝
Thank you.
別客氣
You're welcome.
男：看看這傢伙
MAN: Look at this guy.
他用濃縮咖啡機撥打了所有電話
He's got it all dialed in,\nwith his espresso machine
那甜美的小桃子
and that sweet little peach.
有一天，那將是我
That's gonna be me one day.
你可以隨時來，兄弟
You can come over\nwhenever you want, bro.
大家好？
Hey, guys?
我可以讓你把房子另一邊的污垢拖走嗎？
Can I get you to haul the dirt\non the other side of the house?
我知道它更長，
I know it's longer,
- 但是Nadia和我正試著安靜的早晨 - （講西班牙語）
- but Nadia and I are trying to have a quiet morning.\n- (SPEAKING SPANISH)
- （英文）對 - 不會說英語
- (IN ENGLISH) Right.\n- No speak English.
（很抱歉）抱歉，我會和鮑比談談
(LOUDLY) Sorry.\nI will talk to Bobby.
Si Bobby\nSi. Bobby.
我喜歡這樣做
I love doing that.
（叫聲）
(GRUNTING)
（笑聲）
(LAUGHTER)
（應變）
(STRAINING)
（男人說西班牙語）
(MAN SPEAKING SPANISH)
（全部笑，免責聲明）
(ALL LAUGH, EXCLAIM)
- （男人笑） - （格鬥）
- (MEN LAUGHING)\n- (GRUNTING)
（男士除外）
(MEN EXCLAIM MOCKINGLY)
（所有賄賂）
(ALL GROANING)
（男人笑）
(MEN LAUGHING)
（叫聲）
(GRUNTING)
（所有包裝）
(ALL CACKLING)
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
（英文）記得，當你洗完球衣，冷水時
(IN ENGLISH) Remember, when you're\nwashing the jersey, cold water.
你聽溫柔的迴圈好嗎？
You listen.\nGentle cycle. Okay?
（呼出）
(EXHALES)
（CLEARS THROAT）布埃諾
(CLEARS THROAT) Bueno.
嘿，尊重洗滌說明
Hey, respecting\nthe wash instructions
是尊重團隊的最佳方式
is the best way\nto respect the team.
沒有紅色，他們往往流血！
And no reds, they tend to bleed!
折磨，疲倦，口渴
Tortured, tired, thirsty.
嗨，親愛的！你的第一天怎麼樣？
Hi, honey!\nHow was your first day?
太可怕了我的身體
Terrible. My body.
痛苦每一個部分
Pain. Every. Part.
哦
Oh.
我在車裡
I was in the car...
（喃喃）
(MUMBLING)
我說，“什麼？”（MUMBLING）
And I said, "What?"\n(MUMBLING)
我們需要帶他去醫院嗎？
Do we need to take him\nto the hospital?
- 我說，“鮑比” - 不，不，不
- I said, "Bobby..."\n- No, no, no. No.
他很好他只是需要休息一下
He is fine.\nHe just needs some rest.
休息休息
Rest. Rest.
哦，沒錯
Oh, that's right.
污垢是
Dirt is...
你知道嗎？為什麼不花幾分鐘，
You know what? Why don't you\ntake a few minutes,
在你開始今晚你必須做的所有事情之前？
before you get started on all the\nthings you have to do tonight?
什麼？還有更多？
What? There's more?
（SIGHS）我知道你在記憶中遇到了麻煩，
(SIGHS) I know you're\nhaving trouble remembering,
所以我給你列了一份清單
so I made you a list.
不不不
No, no, no.
我離開這個沙發是不可能的
It's physically impossible\nfor me to get off this couch.
我的意思是，我的腿不再運作
I mean, my legs are\nno longer functioning.
看看
Look. Look.
我想，但我不能
I want, but I can't.
即使我可以移動
And even if I could move...
我不想在這個清單上做任何邪惡的事情
I wouldn't want to do any of\nthe vile things on this list.
（SPITS）
(SPITS)
後面還有幾個
There's a couple more\non the back, too.
（MUZAK PLAYING）
(MUZAK PLAYING)
機械：我知道那傢伙怎麼知道那個人？
MECHANIC: I know that guy.\nHow do I know that guy?
嘿，你在Jiffy Lube工作嗎？
Hey. Do you work\nat Jiffy Lube?
上帝，我希望不是
God, I hope not.
這會讓我發瘋
This is gonna drive me crazy.
這是新醬嗎？味道不同
Is this new sauce?\nIt tastes different.
LEONARDO：是的，我添加了一些東西
LEONARDO: Yeah.\nI added a few things.
一些切碎的洋蔥，一點點紅辣椒
Some chopped onion,\na little red pepper
還有一小撮叫做孜然的東西
and a pinch of something\ncalled cumin.
我無法承受另一碗無味的污水
I couldn't bear another bowl\nof that tasteless slop.
我喜歡它我很喜歡它
I like it.\nI like it a lot.
它更好，對吧？
It's better, right?
我不知道
I don't know.
我覺得我們的麵食太多了
I feel like we've been\nhaving pasta too much.
也許你應該把它混合一點
Maybe you should\nmix it up a little.
好的，我要開始學習
Okay, I'm gonna take\nmine up to study.
嘿，清潔廚房後，不要忘記，這是垃圾日
Hey, after you clean the kitchen,\ndon't forget, it's garbage day.
我現在完全清楚為什麼我阻擋了我的生命，菲奧娜
It's entirely clear to me now why\nI blocked out my life, Fiona.
這是一個可怕的存在
It's a hideous existence.
晚安，夥計們，我愛你
Good night, you guys.\nI love you.
-  OLIVIA：晚安，媽媽 -  MOLLY：愛你
- OLIVIA: Good night, Mom.\n- MOLLY: Love you.
哦，你一定是在開玩笑吧。你筋疲力盡嗎？
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.\nAren't you exhausted?
誰會用窮竭作為不做愛的藉口？
Who would use exhaustion\nas an excuse to not make love?
每個人
Everybody.
（SIGHS）
(SIGHS)
到了棚子，我知道我知道這對我來說也很難
To the shed. I know. I know.\nIt's hard for me, too.
今天工作很好
Nice work today.
（叫聲）
(GRUNTING)
（笑）
(LAUGHING)
（繼續計算）
(CONTINUES GRUNTING)
把它關掉！把它關掉！
Turn it off! Turn it off!
把它關掉！（說西班牙語）
Turn it off!\n(SPEAKING SPANISH)
BOBBY :(英文）喲，我的腦袋把這張貼在我的Snapchat上
BOBBY: (IN ENGLISH) Yo, I'm\ngonna post this on my Snapchat.
兄弟，我會讓你成為一個小海狸
I'm gonna make you\na little beaver, bro.
為什麼我們總是抓住那些糟糕的工作？
How come we always\nget the shit jobs?
- 因為你是非熟練工人！ - （免責聲明）
- Because you're unskilled laborers!\n- (EXCLAIMS)
免費土地，沒有免費午餐的土地
Land of the free,\nno land of the free lunch.
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
（在西班牙語中大喊大叫）
(SHOUTS IN SPANISH)
好的，你是個天才
Okay. You are a genius.
我昨晚睡了七個小時，
I got seven hours\nof sleep last night,
並猜猜她正在做什麼晚餐？
and guess what\nhe's making for dinner?
雞肉串，椰子飯
Chicken skewers, coconut rice.
噢，我想要一個假的丈夫
Aw, I want a fake husband.
（SIGHS）謝謝謝謝
(SIGHS) Thank you. Thank you.
我這周學習的時間比我幾個月都多
I got more studying done this\nweek than I have in months.
也許下次我要你犯罪，
Maybe next time I ask you\nto commit a crime,
你不會跟我打架
you won't fight me on it.
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
（全笑）
(ALL LAUGHING)
BOBBY :(英文）兄弟，你很幸運，你有健忘症
BOBBY: (IN ENGLISH) Bro,\nyou're lucky you have amnesia.
我記得當我以為我是侄子
I remember when I thought\nmy nephew
實際上是gonnado與他的生活
was actually gonna\ndo something with his life.
- 音樂是我的藝術家 - （講西班牙語）
- Music is something. I'm an artist.\n- (SPEAKING SPANISH)
（英文）你在我的沙發上睡覺，兄弟
(IN ENGLISH) You're sleeping\non my couch, bro.
是的，那曲調會改變
Yeah, well,\nthat tune's gonna change
當我感謝格萊美頒獎典禮時，戈多
when I thank you\nat the Grammys, Gordo.
- 哦，是嗎？ - 是的
- Oh, yeah?\n- Yeah.
你最好把它撿起來，你知道我在說什麼嗎？
You better pick it up, dawg.\nYou know what I'm saying?
因為迪亞茲的代謝減少了約30
'Cause the Diaz metabolism\nslows down around 30.
在這看到這個？（講西班牙語）
See this right here?\n(SPEAKS SPANISH)
它不會讓你在圖表上，dawg（SPEAKS SPANISH）
It's not gonna get you on the charts, dawg.\n(SPEAKS SPANISH)
（英文）我有一些工作我不想做
(IN ENGLISH) I got some work\nI don't feel like doing.
- 男人為什麼還戴那頂安全帽？ - （講西班牙語）
- Why do you even wear that hard hat, man?\n- (SPEAKS SPANISH)
（男人笑）
(MEN LAUGHING)
- （笑聲） - （免責聲明）
- (LAUGHS)\n- (EXCLAIMS)
（英文）“像男人一樣行事”（西班牙語中的簡歷）
(IN ENGLISH) "Act like a man."\n(RESUMES IN SPANISH)
（英文）像男人一樣行事
(IN ENGLISH) Act like a man.
（男人笑）
(MEN LAUGHING)
像個男人一樣行事！（講西班牙語）
Act like a man!\n(SPEAKS SPANISH)
（在西班牙語中唱歌）
(SINGING IN SPANISH)
- （英文）明天見，Bobby-好的，兄弟
- (IN ENGLISH) See you tomorrow, Bobby.\n- Okay, brother.
嘿，記住，不要告訴Theresa有關雞肉的事
Hey, remember, don't tell\nTheresa about the chicken parm.
嘿
Hey.
我找到了你的東西
I got you something.
冰凍優酪乳
Frozen yogurt.
就像在Playa上過去的日子一樣
Like the old days on the Playa.
- 什麼？ - 在Playa Tortugas
- What?\n- On the Playa Tortugas.
哦，哦
Oh, oh.
對，是日落
Right. Yeah, the sunsets.
- 是的 - 好時光
- Yeah.\n- Yes. Good times.
我不記得我們喜歡哪種口味，
I couldn't remember\nwhich flavors we liked,
所以我得到了一個分類
so I got an assortment.
謝謝這是
Thanks. This was
你真的很好
really nice of you.
我知道我最近並不是最容易生活的，
I know I haven't been the\neasiest to live with lately,
但我會努力一點
but I'm gonna try\na little harder.
我不能承諾更多，但也許我會驚訝自己
I can't promise a lot harder,\nbut maybe I'll surprise myself.
好吧，繼續這樣做
Well, keep doing this.
也許下次，帶上一些澆頭
Maybe next time,\nbring some toppings.
嗯
Mmm.
芒果我喜歡芒果
Mango. I love mango.
我一直都喜歡芒果嗎？
Have I always loved mango?
只要我認識你
As long as I've known you.
是啊
Ah, yes.
我們年輕的時候
When we were young
並且無法保持彼此的雙手
and couldn't keep\nour hands off each other.
沒有
No.
好的
Okay.
好吧，我會在我的棚子裡
Well... I'll be in my shed.
試著保持良好的態度
Trying to have a good attitude.
只有我和蜘蛛
Just me and the spiders.
哦
Oh.
忘了我的浴室
Forgot my bathroom.
哇哇！
Whew. Whew!
- （MONITOR BEEPING） - （SOFIA SIGHS，Speaking SpANISH）
- (MONITOR BEEPING)\n- (SOFIA SIGHS, SPEAKING SPANISH)
（抽鼻子）
(SNIFFLING)
（英文）我打電話給Leonardo Montenegro獲得死亡證明
(IN ENGLISH) I'm calling to get a death\ncertificate for Leonardo Montenegro.
他在幾周前因鯊魚襲擊而去世
He died a couple of weeks ago\nin a shark attack.
是鯊魚襲擊了嗎？
Yes. An attack by a shark fish?
我想我說得對
I think I'm saying\nthat correctly.
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
黑山
Montenegro.
驢子
Burro.
卷餅
Burrito.
嘿！嘿！
Hey! Hey!
- （英文）謝謝，Bobby-你明白了，兄弟
- (IN ENGLISH) Thanks, Bobby.\n- You got it, bro.
（嘲笑）
(SCOFFS)
- 好吧 - 嘿！
- All right.\n- Hey!
- 嘿！ - 嘿，親愛的！
- Hey!\n- Hey, sweetie!
布埃諾
Bueno.
哦，記得哈塞爾貝克
Oi, remember Hasselbeck.
他的運動方式比人們更值得讚揚
He's way more mobile\nthan people give him credit for.
嘿
Hey.
- 你為什麼不騎？ - 訓練輪沒什麼樂趣
- Why aren't you riding?\n- It's no fun with training wheels.
我從沒教你騎自行車？
I never taught you\nto ride a bike?
沒關係，有些爸爸不能那麼多
It's okay. Some dads\ncan't be around that much.
不，這不好
No, it's not okay.
我現在要解決這個問題
I'm gonna fix this. Right now.
讓我把它放好吧？
Let me just put this away. Okay?
你在這裡做什麼？
What are you doing here?
他們今天讓我們在銀行家工作
They got us working bankers'\nhours today.
無論那是什麼
Whatever those are.
所以，如果你看那些傢伙，那很酷
So then it's cool if you\nwatch those guys,
所以我可以去游泳池？
so I can go to the pool?
是的，確定為什麼不呢？
Yeah, sure. Why not?
感謝爸爸
Thanks, Dad.
- 凱特：嘿，媽媽 - 你會被吹走的
- KATE: Hey, Mom.\n- You're gonna be blown away.
現代高級雜誌稱我的表演偷了這個節目
Modern Senior magazine said\nmy performance stole the show.
Saint Jude wellnessnewsletter邀請我參加封面
And the Saint Jude wellness\nnewsletter featured me on the cover.
這無疑讓我沒有托兒服務
That certainly justifies\nleaving me without childcare.
生命的短暫，凱特
Life's short, Kate.
你必須讓你快樂
You gotta do\nwhat makes you happy.
我不想後悔
I don't wanna have regrets
只是因為我沒有想做的事情
just because I didn't do\nwhat I wanted to do.
親愛的，你有一天會明白的
You'll understand\nsomeday, honey.
媽的，我得走了
Shit! I gotta go, Mom.
每個人都在尋找
Everyone's looking.
我不在乎！
I don't care!
我問你一個月，只看你的姐妹們
I asked you for one month,\njust watch your sisters.
- 我們甚至都不知道這個人 - （SCOFFS）
- And we don't even know anything about this guy.\n- (SCOFFS)
這是誰的錯？我沒有讓他進入房子
Whose fault is that? I didn't\nbring him into the house.
這不是重點
That's not the point.
我會告訴你為什麼兩分鐘
And I'll tell you why\nin two minutes.
我們不是在談論這個！
We're not done\ntalking about this!
而且因為你，他們的披薩很冷
And because of you,\ntheir pizza was cold
他們給了我一個糟糕的小費
and they gave me a lousy tip.
也許你有一個糟糕的提示，因為你像鴨子一樣奔跑
Maybe you got a bad tip\nbecause you run like a duck.
你最好希望一切都好
You better hope\neverything's okay.
我討厭這個，我討厭這件事，這太愚蠢了
I hate this. I hate this\nwhole thing. It's so stupid.
（兒童和萊昂納多的尖叫）
(KIDS AND LEONARDO SCREAMING)
奧利維亞：我喜歡海鷹隊！
OLIVIA: I love the Seahawks!
我們的球隊剛剛將球傳到終點線
Our team just ran the ball\nto the finish line.
結束區我們一直在這
The end zone.\nWe've been over this.
哦，正確的觸地得分
Oh, right. Touchdown.
它慢慢回來了
It's coming back slowly.
看，媽媽，一切都很好沒人死
See, Mom, everything's fine.\nNo one died.
哦，凱特，我有一些幫我修好屋頂漏水的人
Oh, and, Kate, I got some of the guys\nto help me fix that leak in the roof.
你拆開包裝盒了嗎？
And you unpacked the boxes?
哦，是的，是的，我找到了這些枕頭
Oh, yeah, yeah.\nAnd I found these pillows.
沙發需要飛濺的顏色
The couch needed\na splash of color.
（講法語）
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
什麼？
What?
“一點一點地，鳥築巢”這是法國人
"Little by little, the bird\nbuilds its nest." It's French.
等我說法語
Wait. I speak French.
為什麼我說法語？
Why do I speak French?
呃
Uh...
嗯，你是導遊，
Well, you were a tour guide,
並且知道巴黎人喜歡坎昆
and it's well-known\nthat Parisians love Cancun.
對於它的籌碼和薩爾薩舞及其弗拉門戈舞者
For it's chips and salsa\nand its flamenco dancers.
謝謝你羞辱我
Thanks for humiliating me\nfor nothing.
嘿！嘿，我們達成了協定，你沒有堅持下去
Hey! Hey, we had a deal,\nand you didn't stick to it.
你已經停飛了
You're grounded.
誰在乎呢？無論如何，我基本上都是這裡的囚徒！
Who cares? I'm basically\na prisoner here anyway!
- 一個星期！ - 凱特，凱特，凱特嘿
- For a week!\n- Kate, Kate, Kate. Hey.
我可以和你談談一下嗎？
Can I talk to you for a sec?
好的，聽著，你還記得13歲的感覺
Okay, listen, you remember\nwhat it's like to be 13.
我沒有，但你可能會這樣做
I don't, but you probably do.
你在做什麼？
What are you getting at?
沒有電話！
And no phone!
嘿，嘿，我認為你可能就是這樣
Hey, hey, I just think\nmaybe you're being...
我不知道，她有點難過
I don't know,\na little hard on her.
不要告訴我如何撫養我的孩子
Don't tell me how\nto raise my kids.
（SCOFFS）“你的孩子”？
(SCOFFS) "Your kids"?
“你的孩子”？
"Your kids"?
嘿聽好了
Hey. Listen.
只是因為那些女孩不是我的種子，
Just because those girls\nwere not conceived with my seed,
不會讓我任何父親或男人
doesn't make me any less\ntheir father or a man.
當然不是我
Of course not. I just...
我沒有完成
I'm not done.
我所做的就是為這個家庭工作，工作和奴隸
All I do is work and work\nand slave for this family.
我可能沒有把我們放在奢侈的一圈，
I may not have put us\nin the lap of luxury,
但我是提供者
but I'm a provider.
你說的是一個低調
What you said was a low blow.
不公平和傷害性的低打
An unfair and hurtful low blow.
- 親愛的，我 - 低吹
- Honey, I...\n- Low blow.
我需要一些空氣
I need some air.
（講法語）
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
獅子座！
Leo!
我檢查分數後立即
Right after I check the score.
足球評論員：這很好！
FOOTBALL COMMENTATOR:\nAnd it is good!
- 我們輸了 - 亞利桑那州的一場驚人勝利
- We lost.\n- A stunning win for Arizona.
我希望你快樂
I hope you're happy.
- 你要去哪裡？ - 我不知道
- Where are you going?\n- I don't know.
而不是因為我不記得了，嗯？
And not because\nI don't remember, hmm?
因為我不知道
Because I don't know.
（門關）
(DOOR SHUTS)
（呻吟聲）
(GROANS)
我叫Leoand，我是個酗酒者
My name is Leo\nand I'm an alcoholic.
ALL：嗨，獅子座
ALL: Hi, Leo.
說實話，我並沒有記得我的飲酒日
To be honest, I don't really\nremember my drinking days.
- 是的 - 去過那兒
- Yep.\n- Been there.
今晚我和妻子打架了
I got in a fight\nwith my wife tonight.
我站在酒吧外面20分鐘
I stood outside a bar\nfor 20 minutes.
我接近這個
I came this close. This...
但我在這裡
But here I am.
- 所有：繼續回來 - 一次一天
- ALL: Keep coming back.\n- One day at a time.
?血腥凳子，血便，血便\n? Bloody stools
Bloody stools, bloody stools
?抗血小板，血便?\n? Antiplatelet, bloody stools ?
天哪！
Holy shit!
（喘氣）
(GASPS)
（呼出）
(EXHALES)
萊昂納多黑山
Leonardo Montenegro.
是的，他幾周前被你所在地區的一條鯊魚謀殺了
Yeah, he was murdered by a shark in\nyour district several weeks ago.
男：對不起，女士
MAN: Sorry, ma'am.
這四年裡沒有鯊魚襲擊
Haven't had a shark attack\naround here in four years.
真？
Really?
你不需要和其他警察局一起檢查嗎？
Don't you have to check\nwith other police stations?
女士，我向你保證，
Lady, I promise you,
如果有人要鯊魚襲擊，
if anyone's gonna hear\nabout a shark attack,
將會是我
it's gonna be me.
祝你好運
Good luck to you.
嗯
Hmm.
（DOOR OPENS）
(DOOR OPENS)
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey.\n- Hey.
庵
Um...
對不起今晚
Sorry about tonight.
我是應該道歉的人
I'm the one\nwho should apologize.
不，我真的需要保持街邊清潔
No, I really need to keep\nmy side of the street clean
而且，你知道，培養一種感恩的態度
and, you know, cultivate\nan attitude of gratitude.
我反應過度，我和艾米麗說話並且沒有接觸她
I overreacted. I talked\nto Emily and ungrounded her.
我對此測試非常緊張
I'm just so stressed out\nabout this test.
好吧，你一直在努力工作
Well, you've been\nworking so hard and...
（計時器BEEPS）
(TIMER BEEPS)
我知道了
I got it.
而且我一直在想我可以提供幫助
And I've been thinking\nhow I can help.
所以我和特麗莎談過
So I talked to Theresa
她可以通過挑選你的一些轉變來做到這一點
and she's okay with me\npicking up a few of your shifts.
- 真的嗎？你會為我做那件事嗎？ - 是的
- Really? You'd do that for me?\n- Yeah.
我不是無私的
I'm not being selfless.
我只是在想自己
I'm just thinking\nof myself less.
你喜歡用牛奶，對吧？
You like it with milk, right?
還有一點糖
And a little sugar.
哦，我星期天帶孩子們一起去學習
Oh, and I'll take the kids\nall day Sunday so you can study.
你自己？我不能讓
By yourself? I can't let...
實際上，這將是驚人的
Actually, that would be amazing.
大
Great.
我也在想我應該哦！啊！
I was also thinking\nthat I should... Oh! Ah!
鋒利的刀血血血
Sharp knife. Blood. Blood.\nLots of blood.
- 我不喜歡血 - 好吧
- I do not like blood.\n- All right.
- 好吧，放輕鬆你好 - （PANTING）
- All right, take it easy. You're okay.\n- (PANTING)
- 讓我看看，讓我看看 - 幫助
- Let me see, let me see.\n- Help.
我要把它洗掉
I'm just gonna wash it off.
- 感到不安會暈倒 - （水跑）
- Feeling queasy. Gonna faint.\n- (WATER RUNNING)
不，你不會暈倒
No. You're not gonna faint.
- 我暈倒了 - 不
- I'm fainting.\n- No.
房間在旋轉
The room is spinning.
好吧，讓我們來到這裡吧
All right, let's just\nsit you down over here.
（呼吸困難）有多糟糕？
(BREATHING HEAVILY)\nHow bad is it?
我應該去醫院嗎？我需要止血帶嗎？
Should I go to the hospital?\nDo I need a tourniquet?
放鬆你是一個訓練有素的專業人士
Relax. You are\nwith a trained professional.
- 我需要縫針嗎？ - 不
- Do I need stitches?\n- No.
請幫幫我，我要流血至死
Please help me.\nI'm bleeding to death.
哦，天哪！真的很深
Oh, God! It's really deep.
（格魯斯）你到底在幹嘛？
(GROANS)\nWhat the hell are you doing?
清理切割我的上帝，你真是個孩子！
Cleaning the cut.\nMy God, you're such a baby!
（呻吟）
(GROANING)
我懂了
I got this.
我上了全班
I took a whole class on it.
敷料傷口？
Dressing wounds?
處理歇斯底里的病人
Dealing with\nhysterical patients.
（笑）
(CHUCKLES)
好吧
All right.
好的
Okay.
那裡
There.
你有很好的方式
You have very good\nbedside manner.
- 你這麼認為？ - 是的
- You think so?\n- Yeah.
有時我擔心這一點
Sometimes I worry about that.
不，你是天生的
No. No, you're a natural.
好吧那你就像新的一樣好
All right. There you go.\nGood as new.
嗯，嗯
Well, um...
（SIGHS）我想我會讓你學習
(SIGHS)\nI guess I'll let you study.
謝謝你們好好照顧我
Thanks for taking\nsuch good care of me.
好的
Okay.
晚安
Good night.
等待
Wait.
你可以睡在樓下，在沙發上
You can sleep inside.\nDownstairs, on the couch.
（喘氣）
(GASPS)
你讓我很開心
You've made me very happy.
（拉丁音樂劇）
(LATIN MUSIC PLAYING)
（在西班牙語中唱歌）
(SINGING ALONG IN SPANISH)
（CRYING和YELLING）
(CRYING AND YELLING)
（CRYING）
(CRYING)
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
（SIGHS）
(SIGHS)
（INDISTINCT CHATTER）
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
我們會在比賽結束後接你，嗯？
We'll pick you up\nafter the game, hmm?
別客氣！
You're welcome!
我們為什麼不去游泳？
Why can't we go swimming?
我們給你的sistera一點空間
We're giving your sister\na little space.
（發動機起動）
(ENGINE STARTS)
（笑）
(LAUGHING)
空間太大
Too much space.
我們給了她太多的空間
We're giving her too much space.
艾米莉：每個人都在看
EMILY: Everyone's watching.
LEONARDO：我不在乎！
LEONARDO: I don't care!
我沒有聽你的話你甚至不是我真正的爸爸
I don't have to listen to you.\nYou're not even my real dad.
什麼？你媽媽告訴你的？
What? Your mother told you?
好吧，我還是不讓你扔掉自己的生命
Well, I'm still not letting\nyou throw your life away
對於一些性感瘋狂，卷髮的狼
for some sex-crazed,\ncurly-haired wolf.
那個男孩只想要一件事和一件事
That boy wants one thing\nand one thing only.
他是同性戀
He's gay.
好的一件事
Okay. One different thing.
（CRIES SOFTLY）
(CRIES SOFTLY)
你在做什麼？你為什麼哭？
What are you doing?\nWhy are you crying?
因為我很悲慘
Because I'm miserable.
你是？
You are?
是啊
Yeah.
我在波特蘭真的很受歡迎，
I was really popular\nin Portland,
在這裡，每個人都在小組中，我不是其中的一員
and here everyone's on group\ntexts that I'm not a part of.
這個男孩在我喜歡的西班牙語課上，
And there's this boy in\nmy Spanish class that I like,
但他不知道我存在
but he doesn't know\nthat I exist.
他和這裡的救生員是朋友，那就是
And he's friends with the\nlifeguard here and that's...
- 等等，你正在服用西班牙語？ - （SPEAKS SPANISH）
- Wait, you're taking Spanish?\n- (SPEAKS SPANISH)
很好
Muy bien.
（英文）你的發音非常自然
(IN ENGLISH) Your pronunciation\nis very natural.
我的意思是，你還需要滾動“R”
I mean, you still need\nto roll the "R's".
- （講西班牙語） - 什麼？
- (SPEAKS SPANISH)\n- What?
（講西班牙語）說出來
(SPEAKS SPANISH) Say it.
- 你必須好的，好的 - 爸爸！
- You have to... Okay, okay.\n- Dad!
怎麼可能不知道你存在？
How could he\nnot know you exist?
你是一個美麗，聰明，體貼的年輕女子
You're a beautiful, smart,\nthoughtful young woman.
他很幸運能成為你的男朋友
He'd be lucky\nto be your boyfriend.
但你對男朋友來說太年輕了
But you're way too young\nfor a boyfriend.
他們都很幸運能成為你的男朋友
They'd all be lucky\nto be your boyfriend.
這裡的每個男孩都應該成為你的男朋友
Every boy here should beg\nto be your boyfriend.
但我禁止它，我禁止它！
But I forbid it. I forbid it!
我知道我已經在地圖上了
I know I'm all over the map.\nIt's just...
女兒非常困惑
It's very confusing\nhaving a daughter.
看，我不會做任何蠢事好嗎？
Look. I'm not gonna do\nanything stupid. All right?
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
格拉西亞斯
Gracias.
Blue 52熱門航線離開了
Blue 52. Hot route left.
小屋，小屋，徒步旅行！
Hut, hut, hike!
（WHOWLE BLOWS）
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
是的是的！
Yes! Yes!
去，去，去是的！是的！是的！
Go, go, go. Yes! Yes! Yes!
GO！GO！GO！是的！
Go! Go! Go! Yes!
（吹噓）
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
- 嗚嗚！ - （笑）
- Woo-hoo!\n- (LAUGHS)
- 是啊！
- Yeah!\n- Yeah!
- 去團隊！是的，我們做到了！ - 那是我的女兒
- Go team! Yeah, we did it!\n- That's my daughter.
我們知道
We know.
第二次達陣
Second touchdown.
（笑）
(CHUCKLES)
實際上，我們贏了
We're winning, actually.
KID：是的，我們踢了他們的屁股！
KID: Yeah,\nwe kicked their butts!
- 凱特：謝謝你救我 - 萊昂納多：啊
- KATE: Thanks for rescuing me.\n- LEONARDO: Ah.
凱特：我的思緒變得糊裡糊塗
KATE: My mind was\nturning into mush.
嘿，莫莉！
Hey, Molly!
你什麼時候學習如何沒有訓練輪子？
When did you learn how to ride\nwithout training wheels?
爸爸教我
Dad taught me.
（CLICKS TONGUE）
(CLICKS TONGUE)
她只跌倒了一次
She only fell once.
快！快！快！
Faster! Faster! Faster!
- 來吧，來吧，來吧！是的，是的，是的！ - （MOLLY GIGGLING）
- Come on, come on, come on! Yes, yes, yes!\n- (MOLLY GIGGLING)
喔！
Whoo!
LEONARDO：那麼如何擺脫大腦凍結呢？
LEONARDO: So how do I get rid\nof the brain freeze?
- 像這樣 - 像這樣？
- Go like this.\n- Like this?
- （GRUNTS）Mmm-（GIGGLES）
- (GRUNTS) Mmm.\n- (GIGGLES)
（笑著）
(CHUCKLING)
你要離開我們嗎？
Are you gonna leave us?
你什麼意思？當然不是我爸爸
What do you mean?\nOf course not. I'm your dad.
爸爸有時會離開
Sometimes dads leave.
嗯，我想也許他們這樣做，但我不會去任何地方
Well, I guess maybe they do,\nbut I'm not going anywhere.
你被我困住了
You're stuck with me.
謝謝（CHUCKLING）
Thank you. (CHUCKLING)
（軟）“突然體重增加B腹部癢
(SOFTLY) "A. Sudden weight gain.\nB. Abdominal itch.
“C血腥凳子D輕”（卡車軟）
"C. Bloody stools. D. Light..."\n(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
血便
Bloody stools.
（古典音樂劇）
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
（口吃）
(STAMMERS)
（喘氣）
(GASPS)
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
艾，爸爸！
Ay, Papa!
爸爸！
Papa!
（喘氣）
(GASPS)
（不包括喜歡）
(EXCLAIMS WITH JOY)
（英文）科林，你是馬格達萊納的
(IN ENGLISH) Colin,\nwere you with Magdalena
當她確定我哥哥的身體？
when she identified\nmy brother's body?
不，女士，她非常堅持自己處理這件事
No, ma'am, she was quite insistent\non handling the matter herself.
你在暗示嗎？
Are you insinuating?
我應該暗示嗎？
Should I be insinuating?
在回答之前，請記住我是蘇格蘭人
And before you answer that,\nremember I'm Scottish.
我可以整天這樣做
I can do this all day long.
（INDISTINCT CHATTER）
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
嘿！那麼，考試？
Hey! So, the test?
有一對我被淘汰了，但至少它已經結束了
There was a couple that I blanked\non, but at least it's over.
現在我沒有必要跟上這個瘋狂的謊言
Now I don't have\nto keep up this insane lie.
在你告訴他之前，你確定你不想等幾周嗎？
Are you sure you don't wanna wait a\ncouple of weeks before you tell him?
我的意思是，很難找到很好的幫助
I mean, good help\nis hard to find.
是的，完全和那些傢伙也開始喜歡他了
Yeah, totally. And the guys are\nreally starting to like him, too.
不，不公平是公平的，他已償還債務
No. No. Fair is fair.\nHe has paid his debt.
我已經折磨了他足夠長的時間
I have tortured him\nlong enough.
好的
Okay.
你真的會再次討厭自己的洗衣店
You're really gonna hate\ndoing your own laundry again.
（SIGHS）夥計們
(SIGHS) Guys...
我感到非常緊張
I feel pretty nervous.
我想他會嚇壞的
I think he's gonna freak out.
BOBBY：嚇壞了？
BOBBY: Freak out?
你知道，凱特，你說的是挖溝工人的億萬富翁
Kate, you're telling a ditch digger\nhe's a billionaire, you know.
我很確定它會好起來的
I'm pretty sure\nhe's gonna be okay with it.
是啊
Yeah.
嘿
Hey.
呃，我需要和你談談
Uh, I need to talk to you.
是的什麼事？
Yeah. What's up?
我必須承認一些事情，我不知道從哪裡開始
I have to confess something,\nand I don't know where to start.
好吧，不管它是什麼，
Well, whatever it is,
我相信這不是什麼大不了的事
I'm sure it's not\nthat big of a deal.
- 它很大 - 是嗎？
- It's pretty big.\n- Yeah?
這聽起來很瘋狂
And this is gonna sound crazy.
也許搞笑 - 瘋狂瘋狂
Maybe funny-crazy\nor crazy-crazy.
但我做了一件可怕的事情
But I did something terrible.
- （計時器嗶嗶聲） - 堅持這個想法
- (TIMER BEEPING)\n- Hold that thought.
女孩！
Girls!
晚餐準備好了！
Dinner's ready!
是的，請坐下
Yeah. Sit down, please.
- 小心，它很熱 - 聞起來很香
- Be careful, it's hot.\n- It smells so good.
-  MOLLY：我希望它的味道很好 -  OLIVIA：它看起來很棒
- MOLLY: I hope it tastes good.\n- OLIVIA: It looks so good.
用勺子嗯
Use a spoon. Mmm.
所以
So...
什麼是你需要承認的可怕的事情？
What's this awful thing\nyou need to confess?
一世
I...
來吧，我是你的丈夫你可以告訴我任何事情
Come on, I'm your husband.\nYou can tell me anything.
（SIGHS）
(SIGHS)
我忘了這是我們的周年紀念日
I forgot it's our anniversary.
真的嗎？（笑）
Really? (CHUCKLES)
今天？
Today?
周年快樂！
Happy anniversary!
我們出去了！
We're going out!
- （BAND PLAYING UPBEAT LATIN MUSIC） - （在西班牙語中唱歌）
- (BAND PLAYING UPBEAT LATIN MUSIC)\n- (SINGING IN SPANISH)
（CROWD APPLAUDING）
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
你們真的很好
You guys are really good.
謝謝，兄弟告訴我的叔叔
Thanks, bro. Tell my uncle.
LEONARDO：十五年
LEONARDO: Fifteen years.
很多夫妻都不會那麼久
A lot of couples don't\nmake it that long.
是啊
Yeah.
謝謝你堅持我
Thanks for sticking with me.
我知道我沒有成功
I know I haven't made\nthings easy.
- 這裡很漂亮 - 漂亮
- It's pretty out here.\n- Beautiful.
（SHIPS HORN HONKING）
(SHIPS HORN HONKING)
你知道當aship這樣三次鳴喇叭時意味著什麼嗎？
Do you know what it means when a\nship honks three times like that?
有人告訴我一次，但我忘記了
Someone told me once,\nbut I forgot.
是的，我願意
Yes, I do.
它基於古老的西班牙傳奇
It's based on\nan old, Spanish legend.
- （笑） - 是的
- (LAUGHS)\n- Yeah.
順便說一句，很浪漫
Very romantic, by the way.
你看，有一個名叫卡塔利娜的窮人女僕
You see, there was a poor\nhousemaid named Catalina.
她非常漂亮，引起了殖民地州長的兒子阿圖羅的注意
She was very pretty and caught the eye\nof the colonial governor's son, Arturo.
好的，等你沒有記住任何東西，
Okay, wait. You don't\nremember anything,
但你還記得嗎？
yet you remember this?
這是一個非常著名的傳奇
It's a very famous legend.
所以，他們墜入愛河
So, they fell in love.
當然
Of course.
但阿圖羅的父親禁止它
But Arturo's father forbade it.
他不可能讓他唯一的兒子與一個平民一起跑
He couldn't have his only son\nrunning around with a commoner.
因此，他命令阿圖羅返回西班牙，他做了
So, he ordered Arturo to return\nto Spain, which he did.
但不是在宣傳卡塔利娜之前
But not before\npromising Catalina
他會回來給她發信號
he'd come back\nand signal for her
有三次長爆炸
with three long blasts.
就像你聽到的一樣
Just like you heard.
這聽起來像廚房人看的節目之一
This sounds suspiciously like one of\nthe shows the kitchen guys watch.
- 我不知道你在說什麼 - 嗯嗯
- I have no idea what you're talking about.\n- Uh-huh.
無論如何，一年後，一切都按計劃進行
Anyway, a year later,\neverything went as planned.
她遊了出去，但霧太厚了
She swam out,\nbut the fog was too thick.
他喊道，“卡塔利娜！卡塔利娜！”
He called out,\n"Catalina! Catalina!"
她大聲喊道，“阿圖羅！阿圖羅！”
She yelled back,\n"Arturo! Arturo!"
然後，他潛入水中
And with that,\nhe dove into the water.
他們重聚，
They reunited,
和卡塔利娜，直到那時為止，
and Catalina, who,\nup until that point,
一直在抵抗他
had been resisting him
因為一些必須要學習的考試，
because of some test\nshe had to study for,
最後讓他親吻她
finally let him kiss her.
嗯
Hmm.
哦，現在我記得
Oh. Now I remember.
三個鳴喇叭意味著一艘船要反過來
Three honks means a boat's\nabout to go in reverse.
（笑）
(LAUGHS)
好的
Okay.
也許事實上
Maybe. Factually.
但是我
But I...
（喘氣）
(PANTING)
這總是這麼好嗎？
Was it always this good?
每次和你一樣喜歡第一次
Every time with you\nis like the first time.
看看這件事，我們建造了它
Look at this thing.\nWe built it.
你的第一個游泳池，兄弟
Your first pool, bro.
- 幹得好 - （笑得很開心）
- Good job.\n- (ALL LAUGH HAPPILY)
嘿，看著你，你現在有了工人的手
Hey, look at you,\nyou got working man hands now.
全部：是的！
ALL: Yeah!
是的，我願意！
Yes, I do!
（所有的笑聲和笑聲）
(ALL SHOUTING AND LAUGHING)
那很好
That's good.
足球評論員：拿起那場比賽，拉肯湯姆林森在那裡下場
FOOTBALL COMMENTATOR: Take that play, get\noff the block there by Laken Tomlinson.
這個傢伙有一天會成為一名防守型MV，我向你保證
This guy will be a defensive\nMVP one day, I guarantee you.
爸爸，什麼是變態？
Dad, what's a pervert?
庵
Um...
嗯，呃
Well, uh...
當一個男人
When a man
有一輛麵包車
has a van...
凱特！
Kate!
莫莉有一個問題要問你
Molly has a question for you.
（呻吟聲）
(GROANS)
是什麼讓他們這麼久？
What is taking them so long?
你會放鬆嗎？
Would you relax?
他們說他們會在下午2點之後發佈結果
They said they were gonna post\nthe results after 2:00 p.m.
LEONARDO：好的中場休息
LEONARDO: All right. Halftime.
我正在吃午飯
I'm getting lunch.
哦，等我的名單在哪裡？
Oh, wait. Where's my list?
這裡
Here.
嗯Ciao
Mmm... Ciao.
凱特：等等！嘿，我忘了
KATE: Wait! Hey, I forgot.
蜜糖！
Honey!
得到涼拌捲心菜，好嗎？也許還有一些薯片
Get coleslaw, okay?\nAnd maybe some potato chips.
好，知道了
Okay, got it.
寫下來我知道你會忘記
Write it down. I know you.\nYou're gonna forget.
並獲得餅乾我想要餅乾
And get cookies. I want cookies.
餅乾
Cookies.
鋼筆
Pen.
凱特！
Kate!
怎麼了？
What's the matter?
我不知道我只是想知道
I don't know.\nI was just wondering
一個不孕男子的妻子會做什麼
what the wife on an\ninfertile man would be doing
帶有帶肋的水庫尖塔木馬？
with a strip of ribbed,\nreservoir-tipped Trojans?
好的（STAMMERS）
Okay... (STAMMERS)
這不是你的想法
This is not what you think.
沒什麼
It's nothing.
什麼都沒有？我們發誓
Nothing? We made a vow.
我想，這是一個神聖的誓言
A sacred vow,\nwhich I kept, I think.
並且不要假設我沒有機會，
And don't assume\nI didn't have opportunities,
因為我做到了
because I did.
可能有很多很多
Lots and lots of them. Probably.
這很堅果
This is nuts.
你知道嗎，我很高興
You know what, I'm glad.
我很高興你找到了這些，
I'm glad you found these,
因為我一直試圖告訴你這個方法
because I have been trying to\nthink of a way to tell you this.
你和我
You and I...
我們真的沒有結婚
We're not really married.
我沒讓你開心嗎？
Have I not made you happy?
是的，但那不是重點
Yes, but that's not the point.
我不是你的妻子
I'm not your wife.
那些孩子在那裡，他們不是你的孩子
Those kids in there,\nthey're not your children.
哦，這又是
Oh, this again.
低衝擊
Low blow.
好的，來吧吧！
All right, come on.\nCome on!
女孩？
Girls?
女孩，我只是告訴他真相，我也想讓你告訴他
Girls, I just told him the truth,\nand I want you to tell him, too.
來吧，告訴他
Go ahead, tell him.
告訴他什麼？
Tell him what?
告訴他他不是你爸
Tell him he's not your dad.
但他是我們的爸爸？
But he is our dad?
不，不要告訴他我告訴你的事情
No, don't tell him\nwhat I told you to tell him.
告訴他什麼真的是艾米麗？
Tell him what really\nhappened. Emily?
他喝醉了，在沙灘上醒了
He got drunk and\nblacked out on the beach.
我們真的很擔心我無法入睡
We were really worried.\nI couldn't sleep.
不，該死！告訴他真相！
No, damn it!\nTell him the truth!
難道你不是那樣說三個火槍手嗎？
Don't you speak to\nmy three musketeers like that.
我有它
I've had it.
你覺得你在做什麼？
What do you think you're doing?
- 我們喜歡他 - 我們想留住他
- We like him.\n- We want to keep him.
你不能留住他，他不屬於你
You can't keep him.\nHe doesn't belong to you.
他也不屬於你，但這並沒有阻止你
He didn't belong to you, either,\nbut that didn't stop you.
- 你知道我有我的理由 - 我們也是
- You know I have my reasons.\n- So do we.
獅子座，聽著看，看，看看這些安全套不是凱特的
Leo, listen. Look, look, look.\nThose condoms aren't Kate's.
它們是我的
They're mine.
不要為她遮掩
Don't cover for her.
不，我不是在為我報導
No, I'm not.\nShe's covering for me.
是的，我是與客戶打交道的人
Yeah. I'm the one\nsleeping with the customers.
（SCOFFS）真的嗎？
(SCOFFS) Really?
我有一個問題，LeoI癡迷於性
I have a problem, Leo.\nI'm obsessed with sex.
來吧
Come on.
我是性癮者！這是真的
I'm a sex addict!\nIt's a real thing.
你在說什麼？
What are you talking about?
凱特！我坦白道
Kate! I confessed.
你不必再騙我了
You don't have to lie\nfor me anymore.
我終於得到了我需要的?明
I can finally get\nthe help I need.
現在，別擔心，你不必告訴鮑比
Now, don't worry.\nYou don't have to tell Bobby.
我會告訴他
I'll tell him.
你恨我嗎？
Do you hate me?
（SIGHS）
(SIGHS)
當然不是
Of course not.
我知道肉體很脆弱
I know the flesh is weak.
嘿，有一天一次嗯？
Hey, one day at a time. Hmm?
是的，一次一天
Yeah, one day at a time.
（呼出）
(EXHALES)
我很抱歉我不相信你
I'm so sorry I didn't trust you.
這真讓我害怕
That really scared me.
這就像我的一生都是謊言
It was like my whole life\nwas a lie.
奧利維亞：來吧，他們又回到了球場上！
OLIVIA: Come on,\nthey're back on the field!
嘿，下半場即將開始
Hey. Second half's\nabout to start.
介意做三明治嗎？
Mind doing the sandwich run?
你在做什麼？
What are you doing?
我無法永遠保持這種狀態
I can't keep this up forever.
為什麼不？
Why not?
好的，看，我知道你們的關係有點不同尋常
Okay, look, I know your relationship's\na little unconventional.
但誰不是？你們在一起很好
But whose isn't?\nYou guys are good together.
停止戰鬥吧
Stop fighting it.
我會告訴你一件事
I'll tell you one thing.
假裝與否，Bobby的拉丁語egois不喜歡被欺騙
Pretend or not, Bobby's Latin ego\nis not gonna like being cheated on.
-  LEONARDO：凱特！ - 屎
- LEONARDO: Kate!\n- Shit.
他們告訴他
They told him.
你過去了！你是一名護士！
You passed! You're a nurse!
（尖叫）
(SCREAMING)
（所有的選擇）
(ALL CHEERING)
MOLLY：恭喜，媽媽！
MOLLY: Congratulations, Mom!
（GIRLS GIGGLING）
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
- 遠足！ - 讓我們這樣做
- Hike!\n- Let's do this.
（叫喊）
(YELLS)
- 嘿，戈多 - 嘿
- Hey, Gordo.\n- Hey.
你還好嗎？
You okay?
咦？呵呵
Huh? Oh.
是的，嗯，你知道，我做得更好
Yeah, well, you know,\nI've been better.
是啊
Yeah.
但這是我們需要的喚醒電話
But this is the\nwake-up call we needed.
我不像以前那樣關心她的需要
I wasn't as attentive to her\nneeds as I should have been.
你知道，我可以在遠方，也可以
You know, I can be\nemotionally remote, bro.
我們開始夫妻治療
We're starting couples therapy.
- 哦，好 - 是的
- Oh, good.\n- Yeah.
只是，無論你做什麼，你知道，不要
Just, whatever you do,\nyou know, don't...
對不起，以Katefor授予因為
I'm sorry, take Kate\nfor granted. Because...
（SIGHS）
(SIGHS)
看，我知道我們可以成為一個小小的機器人
Look, I know we can be\na little machista.
- 這是我們的方式是的 - 你知道嗎？
- It's our way. Yeah.\n- You know?
但是你的脆弱和誠實真的觸動了我
But your vulnerability\nand honesty really touches me.
- （兩個夾子） - （講西班牙語）
- (BOTH CHUCKLE)\n- (SPEAKS SPANISH)
（MOUTHS）你欠我的
(MOUTHS) You owe me.
（MOUTHS）我知道
(MOUTHS) I know.
哦，是的，這是一張聖誕賀卡
Oh, yeah,\nthis is a Christmas card.
艾米莉：哦，天啊，天氣很冷！
EMILY: Oh, God, it's cold!
萊昂納多：我找到了你！
LEONARDO: I got you!
機械：那是他的雞鬥人
MECHANIC: That's him.\nThe chicken fight guy.
（手機殼）
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
（SOFIA說西班牙語）
(SOFIA SPEAKING SPANISH)
（流鼻涕）
(SNIFFLES)
（播放古典音樂）
(PLAYS CLASSICAL MUSIC)
（英文）抱著灰燼！抱歉，抱歉
(IN ENGLISH) Hold the ashes!\nSorry, sorry.
（清嗓子）
(CLEARS THROAT)
這是在20分鐘前拍攝的
This was taken 20 minutes ago.
- 萊昂納多？ - 什麼？
- Leonardo?\n- What?
這是萊昂納多！（講西班牙語）
It's Leonardo!\n(SPEAKING SPANISH)
（所有語言不一致）
(ALL SPEAK INDISTINCTLY)
嘿，夥計們！你們！
Hey, you guys! You guys!
在我切蛋糕之前，
Before I cut the cake,
我只是想感謝你們在這裡
I just want to thank you all\nfor being here.
沒有你們，我無法通過測試
I could not have passed\nthe test without you all.
- 護士凱特！ - 全部：護士凱特！
- Nurse Kate!\n- ALL: Nurse Kate!
特別是你，獅子座
Especially you, Leo.
他煮了，他打掃乾淨了
He cooked, he cleaned.
他做了兩份工作，他讓我笑
He worked two jobs,\nhe kept me laughing.
如果你還沒有嘗試過empanadas，
And if you haven't tried\nthe empanadas yet,
他們很好吃他們
they are delicious.\nHe made them.
他們走了！
They're gone!
（全笑）
(ALL LAUGHING)
什麼，寶貝？
What, babe?
- 他們很好吃，兄弟 - （KATE SPEAKS SPANISH）
- They're delicious, bro.\n- (KATE SPEAKS SPANISH)
（所有免責聲明）
(ALL EXCLAIM)
（英文）等等，等等
(IN ENGLISH) Wait, wait, wait.
等等，等等
Wait, wait, wait.
我也想說些什麼
I want to say something, too.
我的意思是，看看這張臉
I mean, look at this face.
- 看看這張臉 - 哦！
- Look at this face.\n- Oh!
這不是你見過的最漂亮的臉蛋嗎？
Isn't this the most beautiful\nface you've ever seen?
第二秒最美
Second. Second most beautiful.
（全笑）
(ALL LAUGHING)
她對你太好了！
She's too good for you!
而且，我不記得我第一次這樣做，
And also, I don't remember\nthe first time I did this,
這感覺不對
and that doesn't feel right.
所以，凱特，
So, Kate,
你願意再嫁給我嗎？
will you marry me again?
- （GASPS） - 神聖的廢話
- (GASPS)\n- Holy crap.
是啊
Yeah.
是的，是的，我會的！
Yes! Yes, I will!
- 她說是的！ - 她說是的！
- She said yes!\n- She said yes!
（選擇和尖叫）
(CHEERING AND SCREAMING)
這就是我在說什麼，獅子座！
That's what\nI'm talking about, Leo!
去吧，媽媽！
Go, Mom!
那就是我在說什麼，兄弟！
That's what\nI'm talking about, bro!
那是我的孩子
That's my boy right there.
好的，那就是愛，寶貝
Okay, that's love, baby.
“'現在，先生們，'阿塔格南說，不停地解釋他的行為，
"'And now, gentlemen, ' said d'Artagnan,\nwithout stopping to explain his conduct,
“'所有之一，我為人人
"'all for one, and one for all.
“'這是我們的座右銘，不是嗎？
"'That is our motto, is it not?
“'但是，看看這裡'”
"'But still, look here.'"
- （INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER） - （GIRLS GIGGLING）
- (INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)\n- (GIRLS GIGGLING)
- （所有GASP） -  LEONARDO：哇
- (ALL GASP)\n- LEONARDO: Wow.
這是誰的花式車？
Whose fancy car is that?
MOLLY：太酷了
MOLLY: That's so cool.
（PAPI講西班牙語）
(PAPI SPEAKING SPANISH)
（狗狗隊）
(DOG BARKS)
（英文）嘿，Papi！
(IN ENGLISH) Hey, Papi!
蘇菲亞！
Sofia!
嗨，瑪格達！
Hi, Magda!
讓我把它放在房子裡
Let me just drop this\nin the house.
嘿
Hey.
（FLOORBOARD CREAKING）
(FLOORBOARD CREAKING)
帕皮
Papi.
蘇菲亞
Sofia.
瑪格達（GASPS）
Magda. (GASPS)
哦，天哪，我記得
Oh, my God, I remember.
我是萊昂納多黑山
I'm Leonardo Montenegro.
（GASPS）凱特！
(GASPS) Kate!
我治好了！
I'm cured!
醫生說我的記憶可以突然回來，
The doctor said my memory\ncould come back suddenly,
他是對的
and he was right.
我的意思是，我看到了Papi
I mean, I saw Papi...
我走過房子和噗！
I walked past him into\nthe house and poof!
它回來了！
It came back!
（笑）
(CHUCKLES)
親愛的，問我什麼
Honey, ask me anything.
問我關於我在墨西哥城的童年
Ask me about my childhood\nin Mexico City.
關於我的汽車收藏
About my car collection.
關於我的錢
About my money.
錢我有錢！
Money. I have money!
很多很多錢（笑）
Lots and lots of money.\n(LAUGHS)
這是我一生中最快樂的一天！
This is the happiest day\nof my life!
等待
Wait.
你不是我的妻子
You're not my wife.
你為什麼要讓我思考
Why would you make me think...
你為什麼要這樣對我？
Why would you do that to me?
我知道為什麼
I know why.
你是那個討厭我的可怕的地毯清潔工
You're that awful carpet cleaner\nlady who hates me.
和
And...
這些都是你的孩子
And these are your kids
而你讓我相信
and you made me believe...
天啊
Oh, God.
你欺騙了我
You tricked me.
你用過我
You used me.
獅子座
Leo...
不不不
No, no, no.
我的名字不是獅子座
My name is not Leo.
這是萊昂納多
It's Leonardo.
而且我不屬於你
And I don't belong with you.
而且我不屬於他們
And I don't belong with them.
我會得到我的東西
I'll get my things.
（SIGHS）
(SIGHS)
沒有什麼是我的
There's nothing\nin there that's mine.
物有所值
For what it's worth...
對不起
I'm sorry.
和
And...
- 謝謝 - （PAPI SPEAKING SPANISH）
- And thank you.\n- (PAPI SPEAKING SPANISH)
（泣）
(SOBBING)
嘿
Hey.
女孩
Girls.
艾米莉：別去！
EMILY: Don't go!
奧利維亞：爸爸！爸爸！別去
OLIVIA: Dad! Dad! Don't go.
爸爸！爸爸！
Dad! Dad!
爸！
Dad!
不！不要去，不要去！
No! Don't go, don't go!
等等，不
Wait, no.
MOLLY：爸爸！
MOLLY: Daddy!
爸爸，等等！
Daddy, wait!
歡迎回來，先生
Welcome back, sir.
順便說一句，你的葬禮很可愛
Your funeral was lovely,\nby the way.
我更喜歡爸爸的醬汁
I liked Dad's sauce better.
親愛的，你知道他從來不是你的父親
Sweetie, you know\nhe was never really your dad.
你應該試著阻止他
You should have tried\nto stop him.
我要說什麼？
What was I gonna say?
我欺騙了他，我基本上綁架了那個男人
I lied to him.\nI basically kidnapped the man.
那麼什麼？你顯然愛上了他
So what? You're obviously\ntotally in love with him.
現在有什麼關係？
What does it matter now?
他回到了他的舊生活，
He's back to his old life,
與他的僕人和超級名模
with his servants\nand supermodels.
結束了
It's over.
現在結束了，'因為格蘭瑪迫不及待地想看到你
Now finish up, 'cause\nGrandma can't wait to see ya.
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
（笑）
(CHUCKLES)
（英文）不，我不喝酒
(IN ENGLISH)\nNo, I don't drink.
等等，等我喝
Wait, wait. I do drink.
科林，把她填滿！
Fill her up, Colin!
是的，這絕對是我的回憶，先生
Yes, that was definitely\nmy recollection, sir.
- 把瓶子給我 - 啊，我在想什麼？
- Give me the bottle.\n- Ah, what was I thinking?
（UPBEAT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING）
(UPBEAT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
（所有唱歌）
(ALL SINGING)
這太可怕了
This is horrifying.
（繼續唱歌）
(CONTINUES SINGING)
她為什麼要這樣做？
Why is she doing this?
因為生命短暫，你不想後悔
Because life's short, and you\ndon't wanna have regrets.
來吧我們得到了獅子座
Come on. We're getting Leo.
好極了！
Yay!
對不起腹瀉請原諒
Excuse us. Diarrhea. Excuse us.
（MOUTHS）你要去哪兒？
(MOUTHS) Where are you going?
- （MOUTHS）我會打電話給你 - 是的，是的，是的！
- (MOUTHS) I'll call you.\n- Yes, yes, yes!
凱特：快點，我們要抓住他
KATE: Hurry up,\nwe gotta catch him.
先生，你應該打電話給我
Sir, you should have called me.
我已經為你準備好了
I'd have gotten that for you.
你知道，這很有趣
You know, it's funny.
我有這艘船10年了，
I've had this boat for 10 years,
我不認為我曾經踩過這裡
and I don't think\nI ever stepped foot in here.
嗯，那是因為你有人
Well, that's because\nyou have people
為你照顧一切
to take care\nof everything for you.
你知道，當我在工作時，
You know, when I was\nworking construction,
我討厭像我這樣豐富的混蛋
I hated rich assholes like me.
嗯
Hmm.
你恨我，科林？你可以說實話
Did you hate me, Colin?\nYou can be honest.
（CHUCKLES）好吧如果我能找到你，先生，
(CHUCKLES) Well. If I may\nremind you, sir,
我得到這份工作的原因是因為最後一位管家是誠實的
the reason I got this job was because\nthe last steward was honest.
（軟鍵）Eh
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY) Eh.
我可以承認什麼嗎？
Can I confess something?
嗯
Hmm.
我不太確定我適合的地方
I'm not exactly sure\nwhere I fit in anymore.
那太瘋狂了嗎？
Is that crazy?
我們大多數人只知道我們出生的世界
Most of us only know the world\nthat we're born into.
你有幸從完全不同的角度看待生活
You've had the privilege of seeing life\nfrom an entirely different perspective.
是啊，我做了
Yeah, I did.
它吸，不是嗎？
And it sucked, didn't it?
怎麼了，凱特？
What's up, Kate?
鮑比，我們需要你的船！
Bobby, we need your boat!
你聽到了嗎？她需要我的船
You hear that?\nShe needs my boat.
她需要它
She needs it.
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
（英文）“希望墨西哥城的女人
(IN ENGLISH) "There was hope\na Mexico City woman
“附近的遊艇可能是他的妹妹”
"yachting nearby\nmight be his sister."
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
- （BOAT HORN HONKING） - （英文）三
- (BOAT HORN HONKING)\n- (IN ENGLISH) Three.
三個！那是凱特！
Three! That's Kate!
那是凱特
That's Kate.
- 萊昂納多 - （免責聲明）
- Leonardo.\n- (EXCLAIMS)
走開，船長
Move away, Captain.
（同時免除）
(BOTH EXCLAIMING)
阿圖羅！阿圖羅！
Arturo! Arturo!
卡塔利娜！卡塔利娜！
Catalina! Catalina!
（所有的歡呼和尖叫）
(ALL CHEERING AND SCREAMING)
- 奧利維亞：他們正在轉身！ - 艾米莉：媽媽！媽媽！媽媽！
- OLIVIA: They're turning!\n- EMILY: Mom! Mom! Mom!
他們轉過身為什麼他們轉過身來？
They're turning around.\nWhy are they turning around?
- 我不知道 - 鮑比，做點什麼
- I don't know.\n- Bobby, do something.
不不不！
No, no, no!
爸爸！（講西班牙語）
Papa! (SPEAKS SPANISH)
THERESA :(英文）來吧，來吧，我們正在失去他們！
THERESA: (IN ENGLISH) Come on,\ncome on, we're losing them!
這件事能不能更快？
Can't this thing go any faster?
不，這是一艘休閒船，寶貝！
No, it's a leisure boat, babe!
只是承認你多付了
Just admit you overpaid.
好的，好的，我多付了！
Okay, okay, I overpaid!
我們永遠都不會抓住它們
We're never gonna catch them.
我本應該為這個40英尺的球員出擊
I should have sprung\nfor the 40-footer.
對不起，凱特，我無能為力
I'm sorry, Kate.\nThere's nothing I can do.
（發動機STOPS）
(ENGINE STOPS)
我愛你，凱特！
I love you, Kate!
- 我也愛你！ - （SCREAMS）
- I love you, too!\n- (SCREAMS)
他在做什麼？
What's he doing?
- 哦，天哪！ - 哇！太棒了！
- Oh, my God!\n- Whoa! That was amazing!
- 男子落水！ - （講西班牙語）
- Man overboard!\n- (SPEAKING SPANISH)
- 什麼？凱特！ - 媽媽！
- What? Kate!\n- Mom!
- 媽媽！ - 凱特
- Mom!\n- Kate.
我來了！
I'm coming!
媽媽！你在幹嘛？
Mom! What are you doing?
- 你還等什麼？去小艇！ - （講西班牙語）
- What are you waiting for? Get the dinghy!\n- (SPEAKS SPANISH)
（英文）獲得小艇，兄弟！
(IN ENGLISH)\nGet the dinghy, bro!
LEONARDO：我從不想要離開你！
LEONARDO: I never want to be\napart from you!
凱特：我再也不會再去了！
KATE: I'll never\nlet you go again!
萊昂納多！（講西班牙語）
Leonardo! (SPEAKING SPANISH)
- （英文）從來沒有真正進過這件事，兄弟 - （PAPI SPEAKING SPANISH）
- (IN ENGLISH) Never actually been in this thing, bro.\n- (PAPI SPEAKING SPANISH)
媽媽！他在做什麼？
Mom! What is he doing?
我不知道！
I don't know!
我正在談判！
I'm negotiating!
凱特，進去吧！你會被淹死加油！
Kate, get in here!\nYou're gonna drown. Come on!
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
獅子座！
Leo!
（喘氣）
(GASPS)
- （演講挪威語） - （GASPS）
- (SPEAKS NORWEGIAN)\n- (GASPS)
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
親愛的，你來嗎？
Honey, are you coming?
這不是我想像的那一刻
This is not how I envisioned\nthis moment.
我知道我知道
I know. I know.
這只是大多數人實際上
It's just that most people\ndon't actually
必須選擇愛情和金錢
have to choose between\nlove and money.
這不容易（在西班牙語中恢復）
It's not easy.\n(RESUMES IN SPANISH)
（英文）我很容易選擇你
(IN ENGLISH)\nIt's easy. I choose you.
哦，獅子座，你放棄了很多，老兄
Oye, Leo, you're giving up\na lot, dude.
如果你想要花幾分鐘時間，沒有人會嫉妒你
No one would begrudge you if you\nwanted to take a few minutes.
鮑比，你會不會這樣嗎？
Bobby, would you stay\nout of this?
什麼？我只是說！
What? I'm just saying!
愛情消退，好嗎？我的意思是，它很精彩
Love fades, okay?\nI mean, it's wonderful.
但有些激動人心的離開現在，錢
But some of the excitement\ngoes away. Now, money...
鮑比！閉嘴！
Bobby! Shut the hell up!
- 你閉嘴，寶貝！ - 是的！閉嘴！
- You shut up, babe!\n- Yeah! Shut the hell up!
萊昂納多：凱特，聽著
LEONARDO: Kate, listen.
當我和你一起窮的時候，我的生活更加豐富
My life was richer\nwhen I was poor with you
比我擁有世界上所有的錢
than when I had all the money\nin the world.
如果我跳回水中，
If I jump back in the water,
你這次會吻我嗎？
will you promise\nto kiss me this time?
（查克斯）是的
(CHUCKLES) Yes.
（呻吟聲）
(GROANS)
（所有的選擇）
(ALL CHEERING)
- （GROANS） - （BOBBY SPEAKING SPANISH）
- (GROANS)\n- (BOBBY SPEAKING SPANISH)
- （講話） - （少數）
- (SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)\n- (GROANS)
（英文）Go，Kate！
(IN ENGLISH) Go, Kate!
艾（CHUCKLES）
Ay. (CHUCKLES)
（講西班牙語）
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
（英文）去吧，媽媽！
(IN ENGLISH) Go, Mom!
（所有的選擇）
(ALL CHEERING)
午餐完成了！
Lunches are done!
鮑比在五點鐘接我
Bobby's picking me up in five.
好吧你確定今天可以從學校接送女孩嗎？
All right. You sure you can pick\nup the girls from school today?
- 呃，是的 - 我明白了
- Uh, yeah.\n- I got it.
艾米麗，告訴他我要來了
Emily, tell him I'm coming.
是
Yes.
然後我會放棄Oliviaat足球訓練，
Then I'll drop Olivia\nat football practice,
但你必須接她
but you have to pick her up.
- 科林？ - 再次問好
- Colin?\n- Hello again.
（笑聲）地球上有什麼？
(LAUGHING) What on Earth?
（COLIN LAUGHS）
(COLIN LAUGHS)
嘿，過來
Hey, come here.
你在這裡做什麼？
What are you doing here?
我希望你可能會進入市場
I was hoping you might\nbe in the market
為一流的蘇格蘭保姆提供優秀的參考資料
for a top-notch, Scottish nanny\nwith excellent references.
你知道我喜歡那個，
You know I'd love that,
但我們沒辦法讓你負擔得起
but there's no way\nwe can afford you.
嗯，事實上你可以，先生
Well, in fact you can, sir.
索菲亞把我送回了遊艇
Sofia sent me back\nwith the yacht.
她想提醒你
She wanted to remind you
這是你父親的生日禮物
it was a birthday present\nfrom your father.
契約在你的名下仍然是你的
The deed is in your name.\nIt's still yours.
哦，我的上帝
Oh, my God.
你的意思是我可以出售它？
You mean I can sell it?
它一定值得一大筆錢
It must be worth a fortune.
超過6000萬
Over 60 million.
比索？
Pesos?
上帝，不，女士美元
God, no, ma'am. Dollars.
哦
Oh.
（笑）
(LAUGHING)
（尖叫和聆聽）
(SCREAMING AND CHEERING)
靠挪威皇家海軍投資的力量，
By the power invested in me\nby the Royal Norwegian Navy,
我現在宣佈你的丈夫和妻子
I now pronounce you\nhusband and wife.
（兒童節目）
(KIDS SCREAMING)
- 去吧，媽媽！ - 去吧，媽媽！
- Go, Mom!\n- Go, Mom!
艾米莉：去吧，爸爸！
EMILY: Go, Dad!
（所有的選擇）
(ALL CHEERING)
（玻璃貼心）
(GLASS CLINKING)
BOBBY：好的
BOBBY: Okay.
在我祝福這對幸福的夫妻之前，
Before I toast the happy couple,
讓我消除一些謠言
let me just dispel a few rumors
一直漂浮在周圍
that have been floating around
關於我被騙了
about me being cheated on.
從來沒有發生好嗎？不是一次，不是永遠
Never happened. Okay?\nNot once, not ever.
我想說的非常多
There's just so much\nI wanna say.
但我不是詩人
But I'm not a poet.
我沒有話語
I don't have words.
- 我有音樂 - （EMILY SPEAKING SPANISH）
- I have music.\n- (EMILY SPEAKING SPANISH)
（英文）我很抱歉，我無法與你一起慶祝
(IN ENGLISH) I'm so sorry I couldn't\nbe there to celebrate with you.
但我在菲律賓，
But I'm here in the Philippines,
帶頭開展Montenegros'Children教育計畫，
spearheading the Montenegros'\nChildren's Education Initiative,
而且，哦，我一直在這裡幫助這些孩子
and, oh, I've been here\nhelping these kids
擁有更快樂，更美好的生活，他們崇拜我
have a happier, better life,\nand they adore me.
- 對吧？ - 不
- Right?\n- No.
在我們第一次見面的時候，
When we first met,
我抓到了好嗎？
I was the catch. Okay?
我是足球運動員
I was the football player.
我是四分衛，好嗎？
I was the quarterback,\nall right?
她甚至沒有做過領隊
She didn't even make\ncheerleader.
她在精神小隊中
She was on the spirit squad.
當我看到獅子座時（VOICE BREAKING）
When I look at Leo...\n(VOICE BREAKING)
當我看著凱特
When I look at Kate...
- 當我看到Leo和Kate-（VITO SPEAKING SPANISH）
- When I look at Leo and Kate...\n- (VITO SPEAKING SPANISH)
（英文）現在，我在後臺
(IN ENGLISH)\nRight now, I'm backstage
在Golden PondRetirement Home，
at the Golden Pond\nRetirement Home,
離幕約五分鐘
about five minutes from curtain.
我在屋頂上玩Hodelin Fiddler
I'm playing Hodel\nin Fiddler on the Roof.
- 我覺得現在是討論津貼的好時機 - （VITO SPEAKING SPANISH）
- And I thought now was a good time to talk about allowance.\n- (VITO SPEAKING SPANISH)
?獅子座有最好的義大利麵條我曾嘗過?\n? Leo has the best spaghetti\nI ever tasted ?
在婚禮上，我從來沒有參與其中
I have never in all my puff\nbeen at a wedding
哪裡有免費酒吧
where there's been a free bar.
通常，最後，（BLEEP）試圖解決這個問題
Usually, at the end, the (BLEEP)\ntries to settle up the bill.
他們是，“哦，不，我沒有
And they're,\n"Oh, no, I didn't have it.
“我只喝啤酒，你（BLEEP）”
"I only had beer,\nyou (BLEEP)"
在婚禮上總有一個（BLEEP）
There's always a (BLEEP)\nat a wedding.
（播放關鍵）
(PLAYING OFF-KEY)
PAPI：萊昂納多（講西班牙語）
PAPI: Leonardo.\n(SPEAKING SPANISH)
（英文）鮑比要我讀一份準備好的聲明
(IN ENGLISH) Bobby has asked me\nto read a prepared statement.
“我從不欺騙我的丈夫
"I never cheated on my husband.
“我永遠不會
"I never would.
- “沒有女人會” - （VITO SPEAKING SPANISH）
- "No woman ever would."\n- (VITO SPEAKING SPANISH)
-  Mwah！ - 乾杯
- Mwah!\n- Cheers.
- （希伯來語中的CHEERS） - 嗯
- (CHEERS IN HEBREW)\n- Mmm.
- 啊！ - （GLASS SMASHES）
- Ah!\n- (GLASS SMASHES)
- 喔！ - （BARKS）
- Whoo!\n- (BARKS)
由exploskull提供的字幕
Subtitles by explosiveskull